<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Jill Archives - Yorba Foundation</title>
	<atom:link href="http://us.yorba.org/tag/jill/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://us.yorba.org/tag/jill/</link>
	<description>USA</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:17:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>What Jill Duggar Did After Leaving The Duggar Family</title>
		<link>http://us.yorba.org/what-jill-duggar-did-after-leaving-duggar-family/</link>
					<comments>http://us.yorba.org/what-jill-duggar-did-after-leaving-duggar-family/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[usyorba]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Movie]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Duggar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jill]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Leaving]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://us.yorba.org/?p=38</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Amazon Prime docuseries Shiny Happy People: Duggar Family Secrets has put Jill Duggar and her husband Derick Dillard in the spotlight, as the former 19 Kids and Counting star gets candid...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/what-jill-duggar-did-after-leaving-duggar-family/">What Jill Duggar Did After Leaving The Duggar Family</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img decoding="async" src="https://static1.srcdn.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/uohdaw623.jpg" /><br />
The Amazon Prime docuseries <a href="https://screenrant.com/tag/shiny-happy-people-duggar-family-secrets/">Shiny Happy People: Duggar Family Secrets</a> has put Jill Duggar and her husband Derick Dillard in the spotlight, as the former 19 Kids and Counting star gets candid about her past and its secrets. A lot has happened between the 32-year-old Jill since she was last seen in the reality TV show. On that program, the devout Baptist Duggar family gave viewers a look into their strict Christian household and day-to-day lives. The show which premiered in September 2008 ended in May 2015, after 10 entertaining seasons, when allegations arose that Josh had molested four of his sisters.<br />
SCREENRANT VIDEO OF THE DAYSCROLL TO CONTINUE WITH CONTENT</p>
<p>Jill had come forward as a victim, but had seemingly forgiven her brother by then. Jill was introduced to her husband Dillard by her father Jim Bob Duggar. Jim had met Derick on a mission trip to Nepal in 2012. Jill and Dillard got married in June 2014. They welcomed two sons (Israel, born in 2015), and Samuel (whom Jill gave birth to in 2017). Jill was brought back to the world of reality TV in a spin-off called Counting On in 2015, along with a few other Duggar family members.</p>
<p> What Did Jill Duggar Do After Leaving Her Family? </p>
<p>Jill and Derick starred in six seasons of Counting On. However, she walked away from the reality TV series in 2017, ahead of its season 7 premiere in 2018. In 2022, Jill and Derick moved into a new home with their growing family, on the border of Oklahoma and Arkansas. “We moved!! It’s been a crazy several weeks for us, but we are finally settling into our new place!” Jill shared in her family blog. <a href="https://www.dillardfamily.com/2022/06/new-house-new-job-new-state/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">DillardFamily</a>. She also revealed that Derick had a new job, He had been sworn in as an attorney in Little Rock, Arkansas, and then started the transfer process for his new public service job as a prosecutor in Oklahoma.</p>
<p>Jill and Derick welcomed their third son, another boy, in July 2022. Jill appears to be a stay-at-home, while Derick is busy with his courtroom job. Jill announced that she would be releasing her Tell-All memoir in 2024. Called Counting the Cost, it outlines the changes they faced, “including lack of respect for boundaries, greed, manipulation, and betrayal,” as per <a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/Cs6dR2uAQAO/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Jill</a>’s Instagram post. Jill then participated in Shiny Happy People: Duggar Family Secrets, which premiered on June 2, 2023.</p>
<p> Why Did Jill Duggar Leave? </p>
<p>Interestingly, Jill is the only Duggar kid who appears in the docuseries. According to <a href="https://www.nickiswift.com/258346/we-finally-know-why-jill-duggar-left-tlc/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">NickiSwift</a>, Jill and her Dillard family stopped filming for Counting On due to backlash. This happened when Derick&#8217;s controversial tweets about transgender co-star Jazz Jennings surfaced online.</p>
<p>In October 2020, Jill and Derick took to their YouTube <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1Yt7lWGck4k" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">DillardFamilyOfficial</a> to reveal that they left because they wanted to focus on pursuing their other passions. They added that they wished to, &#8220;pursue our own goals and everything.&#8221; They also noted that it was a, &#8220;good decision&#8221; for them, even if leaving their lives as reality TV stars behind was, &#8220;difficult.&#8221; They didn&#8217;t shed light on exactly what these goals were at the time.</p>
<p>Jill and Derick weren’t on the, “best terms” with some of her family after having disagreements, but looked forward to having some time to heal. &#8220;There&#8217;s been some distancing there,&#8221; Jill had said about her relationship with her family. However, she did not name any members in particular. In Shiny Happy People: Duggar Family Secrets, Jill looks back at her family’s fall from grace, and Josh&#8217;s scandal, while opening up about her life and upbringing as a Duggar.</p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://www.dillardfamily.com/2022/06/new-house-new-job-new-state/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">DillardFamily</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/Cs6dR2uAQAO/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Jill Duggar Dillard</a>/Instagram, <a href="https://www.nickiswift.com/258346/we-finally-know-why-jill-duggar-left-tlc/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">NickiSwift</a>, <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1Yt7lWGck4k" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">DillardFamilyOfficial</a>/YouTube</p>
<p> <script async defer src="https://platform.instagram.com/en_US/embeds.js"></script></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/what-jill-duggar-did-after-leaving-duggar-family/">What Jill Duggar Did After Leaving The Duggar Family</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://us.yorba.org/what-jill-duggar-did-after-leaving-duggar-family/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
