<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Sports Archives - Yorba Foundation</title>
	<atom:link href="http://us.yorba.org/category/sports/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://us.yorba.org/category/sports/</link>
	<description>USA</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:56:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Conn Smythe odds: Jonathan Marchessault tops list to win playoff MVP</title>
		<link>http://us.yorba.org/conn-smythe-odds-jonathan-marchessault-tops-list-win-playoff-mvp/</link>
					<comments>http://us.yorba.org/conn-smythe-odds-jonathan-marchessault-tops-list-win-playoff-mvp/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[usyorba]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:56:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conn]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jonathan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[list]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marchessault]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MVP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[odds]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[playoff]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Smythe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tops]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[win]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://us.yorba.org/?p=104</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>May 12, 2023; Las Vegas, Nevada, USA; Vegas Golden Knights right wing Jonathan Marchessault (81) warms up before the start of game five of the second round of the 2023 Stanley Cup...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/conn-smythe-odds-jonathan-marchessault-tops-list-win-playoff-mvp/">Conn Smythe odds: Jonathan Marchessault tops list to win playoff MVP</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://images2.minutemediacdn.com/image/fetch/w_850,h_560,c_fill,g_auto,f_auto/https%3A%2F%2Ffansided.com%2Fwp-content%2Fuploads%2Fimagn-images%2F2023%2F06%2F20654564-850x560.jpeg" rel="attachment wp-att-2425421"/>May 12, 2023; Las Vegas, Nevada, USA; Vegas Golden Knights right wing Jonathan Marchessault (81) warms up before the start of game five of the second round of the 2023 Stanley Cup Playoffs against the Edmonton Oilers at T-Mobile Arena. Mandatory Credit: Stephen R. Sylvanie-USA TODAY Sports<a href="https://fansided.com/2023/06/06/aaron-judge-toe-injury-yankees/" rel="prev">Aaron Judge injury update: Things don’t look good for Yankees by Kristen Wong</a><a href="https://fansided.com/2023/06/06/lions-dan-campbell-jared-goff-improvement-sean-mcvay/" rel="next">Lions: Dan Campbell thinks Jared Goff has improved without Sean McVay by John Buhler</a>     The Vegas Golden Knights have taken over as a <a href="https://fansided.com/2023/06/06/golden-knights-stanley-cup-odds-skyrocket-game-2-win/" rel="">sizable favorite to win the Stanley Cup</a> after taking a 2-0 series lead over the Florida Panthers.As a result, the Conn Smythe Trophy odds have also shifted. The award is given to the MVP of the NHL Playoffs and it’s almost always given to a player belonging to the winning team. So, as you’d expect, players on the Golden Knights are starting to float to the top of the odds list.Let’s take a look at the latest odds to win the Conn Smythe heading into Game 3 in Florida.Conn Smythe Trophy oddsConn Smythe Trophy &#8211; 2022-23Odds updated June 6th, 2023, at 4:46 pmJonathan Marchessault is the new betting favorite to win the Conn Smythe Trophy at -105 odds, which is an implied probability of 51.22%.Marchessault has been hot in the playoffs dating back to the last round. He now has 21 points in 19 postseason games, including a three goals and an assist in the first two games against the Panthers.<a href="https://bit.ly/FanSided-Web-DraftKings" class="chakra-linkbox__overlay css-1cst4gr" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">DraftKings</a>New Users: Bet $5 on Any NHL Playoff Game, Get $200 in Bonus Bets Instantly!<a target="_blank" rel="noopener" class="chakra-link css-1hhai3c" href="https://bit.ly/FanSided-Web-DraftKings">New customers only. 21+ (18+ WY) and present in AZ, CO, CT, IL, IN, IA, KS, LA, MD, MI, NJ, NY, PA, TN, VA, WV, WY. All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements. See full terms at sportsbook.draftkings.com/footballterms. Valid 1 per new customer. Minimum $5 deposit and wager required. Rewards issued as non-withdrawable free bets or site credits (i.e. if your wager wins you receive a $200 bonus paid as 8 free bets of $25 each in addition to any cash winnings from original wager). Gambling Problem? Call/text 1-800-GAMBLER (IL/NJ/PA/WV), call/text 1-800-522-4700 (CO/KS/LA/WY), call 1-800-NEXT-STEP or text NEXTSTEP to 53342 (AZ), call 888-789-7777 or visit ccpg.org/chat (CT), call 1-800-BETS-OFF or visit yourlifeiowa.org/gambling (IA), call 1-800-9-WITH-IT or text INGAMB to 53342 (IN), call 1-800-270-7117 (MI), call (877-8-HOPENY) or text HOPENY (467369) (NY), call/text TN REDLINE 1-800-889-9789 (TN) or call/text 1-888-532-3500 (VA).</a>Read moreJack Eichel is second on the odds list, recording 22 points in the 19 games. With that being said, he only six of his points are goals. With goals held at a higher regard than assists, Marchessault has the edge with his 12 goals.The interesting dark horse is Adin Hill, the goaltender for the Golden Knights, at +500. He has quietly been phenomenal in the playoffs, sporting a 2.06 goals against average and a .937 save percentage in 13 games and 11 starts in the playoffs.The favorite at the start of the Stanley Cup Final, Sergei Bobrovsky, has fallen all the way to +1300 after two poor performances in the first two games. He was even pulled from the net in Game 2 after allowing four goals on just 13 shots.If the Golden Knights win Game 3, all Panthers on the odds list are going to continue to fall down the odds board.<a href="https://bit.ly/FanSided-Web-Caesars" class="chakra-linkbox__overlay css-1cst4gr" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Caesars</a>Get Your First Bet on Caesars up to $1,250 When You Bet Any NHL Game!<a target="_blank" rel="noopener" class="chakra-link css-1hhai3c" href="https://bit.ly/FanSided-Web-Caesars">21+ only. Offer valid and must be physically present in AZ, CO, IL, IN, IA, KS, LA, MI, NJ, NY, PA, TN, VA, WV &amp; WY only. New users and first $10+ wager only. Must register with eligible promo code. Bet amount of qualifying wager returned only if wager is settled as a loss. Maximum bet credit $1,250; must be used within 14 days of receipt. Tier Credits and Reward Credits will be added to account within 7 days after qualifying wager settles. Void where prohibited. Know When To Stop Before You Start® Gambling Problem? AZ: Call 1-800-NEXT-STEP; CO, WY, KS (Affiliated with Kansas Crossing Casino): Call 1-800-522-4700; IN: Call 1-800-9-WITH-IT; IA: Call 1-800-BETSOFF; LA: Call 1-877-770-STOP (licensed through Horseshoe Bossier City and Harrah’s New Orleans); MI: Call 1-800-270-7117; IL, NJ, VA, WV, PA (Affiliated with Harrah&#8217;s Philadelphia): If you or someone you know has a gambling problem, crisis counseling and referral services can be accessed by calling 1-800-GAMBLER (1-800-426-2537) or WV: visit 1800gambler.net. TN: Call or text TN REDLINE at 1-800-889-9789. ©2022, Caesars Entertainment. Gambling problem? Call 877-8-HOPENY or text HOPENY (467369). See Caesars.com/promos for full terms. Read More</a>Read more<a href="https://bit.ly/FanSided-Web-FanDuel" class="chakra-linkbox__overlay css-1cst4gr" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">FanDuel</a>Limited Time: Get a No Sweat First Bet up to $2,500 on the NHL Finals!<a target="_blank" rel="noopener" class="chakra-link css-1hhai3c" href="https://bit.ly/FanSided-Web-FanDuel">$10 first deposit required. Up to $2,500 back in free bets if you lose first online real money wager. New customers only. 21+ and present in AZ, CO, CT, IA, IL, IN, LA (permitted parishes only), MD, MI, NJ, NY, PA, TN, VA, WY, or WV. Restrictions apply. See full terms at sportsbook.fanduel.com. Gambling Problem? Call 1-800-GAMBLER (IL/MD/NJ/PA/WV) or visit mdgamblinghelp.org (MD), 1-800-522-4700 (CO/KS/WY), 1-800-NEXT-STEP or text NEXTSTEP to 53342 (AZ), 1-888-789-7777 or visit ccpg.org/chat (CT), 1-800-BETS-OFF (IA), 1-800-9-WITH-IT or text INGAMB to 53342 (IN), 1-877-770-STOP (LA), 1-800-270-7117 (MI), 1-877-8-HOPENY or text HOPENY (467369) (NY), TN REDLINE 1-800-889-9789 (TN), and 1-888-532-3500 (VA).</a>Read more–Game odds refresh periodically and are subject to change.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/conn-smythe-odds-jonathan-marchessault-tops-list-win-playoff-mvp/">Conn Smythe odds: Jonathan Marchessault tops list to win playoff MVP</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://us.yorba.org/conn-smythe-odds-jonathan-marchessault-tops-list-win-playoff-mvp/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lions: Dan Campbell thinks Jared Goff has improved without Sean McVay</title>
		<link>http://us.yorba.org/lions-dan-campbell-jared-goff-improvement-sean-mcvay/</link>
					<comments>http://us.yorba.org/lions-dan-campbell-jared-goff-improvement-sean-mcvay/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[usyorba]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:54:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Campbell]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Goff]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[improved]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jared]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[McVay]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sean]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[thinks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://us.yorba.org/?p=95</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Dan Campbell believes Jared Goff is a better quarterback for him than he was playing for Sean McVay’s Los Angeles Rams.Look at Dan Campbell driving the Jared Goff hype train, man!Together, the...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/lions-dan-campbell-jared-goff-improvement-sean-mcvay/">Lions: Dan Campbell thinks Jared Goff has improved without Sean McVay</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p> Dan Campbell believes Jared Goff is a better quarterback for him than he was playing for Sean McVay’s Los Angeles Rams.Look at Dan Campbell driving the Jared Goff hype train, man!Together, the <a href="http://fansided.com/nfl/teams/detroit-lions">Detroit Lions</a> are well on their way towards building something special. After narrowly missing out on the NFC playoffs a year ago, one could argue that Detroit is the favorite to come out of the NFC North this season. A big reason for that has been the play of Goff. Campbell went as far to say Goff is a better quarterback now than with the Sean McVay <a href="http://fansided.com/nfl/teams/los-angeles-rams">Los Angeles Rams</a>.While I’m sure a lot of it has to do working with offensive coordinator Ben Johnson and quarterbacks coach Mark Brunell, it’s not like Goff was a scrub coming out of Cal. He played for Sonny Dykes and was the No. 1 overall pick by the Rams in the 2016 <a href="http://fansided.com/nfl/nfl-draft">NFL Draft</a> for a reason!Here is what Campbell had to say at the podium on Tuesday when speaking with the media.“His confidence has really grown … he’s a better quarterback than he was [in L.A.], in my opinion… we’ve come lightyears ahead of where he was two years ago when we started teaching him protections.”This is the entire clip of Campbell speaking with the Lions media about Goff and other big topics.The best part is the Lions are finally pulling in the same direction. It had been a while, to be honest.Dan Campbell feels Jared Goff is a better quarterback now with the Detroit LionsLook. I love everything about this comment from Campbell. It is fantastic. Goff always had talent. I remember watching him sling the pill around for Cal when the Golden Bears weren’t the least bit good and I thought to myself, “Oh, there is something here for sure!” Unfortunately, he played for the worst offenses of my lifetime on the 2016 Rams for Jeff Fisher. That would’ve ruined anyone.After not knowing where the sun went, Goff emerged as a Pro Bowl-caliber passer for the Rams for the next four years. Sadly, it wasn’t good enough for McVay, so he convinced owner Stan Kroenke to trade for fellow Georgia boy Matthew Stafford. Together, McVay and Stafford won a <a href="http://fansided.com/nfl/super-bowl">Super Bowl</a>. While the Lions stunk two years ago, they have the better ceiling … because of Goff.Yes, Detroit may have drafted Hendon Hooker out of Tennessee, but I am nowhere near as high on him as I was Goff coming out of Cal. He may be the future of Lions football, or he may just be a backup. Regardless, look for Goff to continue to grow in Johnson’s offense for as long as he remains in Detroit, as well as build on his rapport with Johnson’s potential successor in Brunell.See, Goff throws a beautiful spiral, but does need a savvy offensive mind to set him up for success to make plays down the field. In time, Goff will grow and mature into his late 20s, now that the cerebral part of his game has caught up to his natural gifts as a passer. Either way, I don’t think we’ve seen the best football out of Goff yet. He is why I am so excited about this Lions this season.If Goff plays up to his standard, Detroit could become one of the eight best teams in all of football. </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/lions-dan-campbell-jared-goff-improvement-sean-mcvay/">Lions: Dan Campbell thinks Jared Goff has improved without Sean McVay</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://us.yorba.org/lions-dan-campbell-jared-goff-improvement-sean-mcvay/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>WNBA Week Three: 3 must-see matchups this week</title>
		<link>http://us.yorba.org/wnba-power-rankings-3-best-games-week-3/</link>
					<comments>http://us.yorba.org/wnba-power-rankings-3-best-games-week-3/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[usyorba]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:53:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[matchups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mustsee]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Week]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[WNBA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://us.yorba.org/?p=92</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The WNBA has a full slate of games this week. Which matchups should be at the top of your viewing list?The WNBA season is in full swing and entering week three of...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/wnba-power-rankings-3-best-games-week-3/">WNBA Week Three: 3 must-see matchups this week</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p> The WNBA has a full slate of games this week. Which matchups should be at the top of your viewing list?The <a href="http://fansided.com/wnba/">WNBA</a> season is in full swing and entering week three of action. Awards races are starting to shape up. All-Star <a href="https://twitter.com/alfcorriette/status/1665781517925187585">voting starts tomorrow</a>.With storylines developing across the league, it can be overwhelming to keep up with what’s going on where. With consistent schedule overlap, it can be even more difficult choosing which games to watch.Allow us to help you decide. Here are three must-see games from this week’s WNBA slate.WNBA must-see games this week, June 5-June 12Las Vegas Aces at Connecticut Sun, June 6, 7 p.m. ESTWhere to watch: WNBA League Pass, NBC Sports Boston, Fox 5, SSSENA rematch of last year’s Finals, this might be the most anticipated game of the year, so far. The best part? These two teams also play on Thursday, Jun 8.Once again, this is matchup of the best two teams in the league. The Aces are the lone undefeated team remaining, while the Sun are right behind them at 6-1. The game features <a href="https://fansided.com/2023/06/06/wnba-mvp-ladder-alyssa-thomas-jackie-young/">two current MVP candidates</a> and will be a fun battle of styles. The Aces lead the league in field goal percentage, and hold their opponents to the lowest shooting percentage. The Sun hold opponents to the worst three-point shooting percentage, and have the third-best scoring defense in the league.Despite the familiarity, neither team is the same as the last time they met. The Sun have a new coach, system, and largely new roster. The Aces have much-improved depth, and an improved starting five (shoutout to Candace Parker).Chicago Sky at Los Angeles Sparks, June 9, 10 p.m. ESTWhere to watch: IonTV, WNBA League PassA battle of two scrappy teams who are outperforming expectations, this one should be a fun watch. Plus, it will be Azurá Stevens’ first game against her former team.ROSTER UPDATE: The Los Angeles Sparks announced today that Azurá Stevens has been activated ahead of Tuesday’s game against the Seattle Storm. Full Release: <a href="https://t.co/OiU9fxrzgm">https://t.co/OiU9fxrzgm</a>— LA Sparks PR (@LASparksPR) <a href="https://twitter.com/LASparksPR/status/1665900599324602368?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 6, 2023</a>The Sparks have established a new identity under Curt Miller, while the Sky have doubled down on theirs under James Wade. Both like to play with pace, and have their own quirks that make them interesting.The Sparks are the league’s best at forcing turnovers. The Sky commit the second-most turnovers. Both teams are top three in three-point shooting and top four in assists. This could turn into a high-scoring affair.Phoenix Mercury @ Indiana Fever, June 11, 5 p.m. ESTWhere to watch: CBS Sports, Facebook, IndianaFever, AZ Family 3TV, AZ Family Sports Network 44Five words describe the intrigue in this one: Aliyah Boston versus Brittney Griner. This season’s No. 1 pick will face off against one of the best to ever do it in what will be her (literal) biggest matchup so far.This is also a matchup of two teams in similar spots in the rankings, but vastly different paths there. The Mercury are a veteran team that have been showing their age in a bad way. They have some bad losses against teams they were expected to be better than. Meanwhile, the Fever are a young team showing theirs in the best ways possible. They have played some great, competitive games against some of the league’s best teams.The stylistic matchup is interesting, too. The Fever are the league’s third-best rebounding team, while the Mercury are last. The Mercury also average the most turnovers in the league by a sizable margin, averaging 6.5 more than the Fever do. Still, the Mercury shoot 46 percent from the field, second best in the league, to the Fever’s 40.4, which is tenth. The teams are the top two fouling teams in the league, though, which could be a big factor in this one. <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/wnba-power-rankings-3-best-games-week-3/">WNBA Week Three: 3 must-see matchups this week</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://us.yorba.org/wnba-power-rankings-3-best-games-week-3/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Latest Jacob deGrom injury update is worst-case scenario for Rangers</title>
		<link>http://us.yorba.org/rangers-jacob-degrom-tommy-john-worst-case/</link>
					<comments>http://us.yorba.org/rangers-jacob-degrom-tommy-john-worst-case/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[usyorba]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:50:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[deGrom]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[injury]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jacob]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Latest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rangers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[scenario]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[update]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[worstcase]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://us.yorba.org/?p=81</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Texas Rangers were hoping that ace Jacob deGrom would progress while rehabbing from his elbow injury. Now, his season is over.The Texas Rangers, in need of starting pitching help, made a...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/rangers-jacob-degrom-tommy-john-worst-case/">Latest Jacob deGrom injury update is worst-case scenario for Rangers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p> The Texas Rangers were hoping that ace Jacob deGrom would progress while rehabbing from his elbow injury. Now, his season is over.The <a href="https://fansided.com/mlb/mlb-teams/texas-rangers/">Texas Rangers</a>, in need of starting pitching help, made a huge gamble this past winter. That being, they signed former New York Mets ace Jacob deGrom to a five-year, $185 million contract. While he is one of the best pitchers in the game, he had been unbelievably injury prone the previous two years. But, the Rangers hoped that they could have him at full health.On Monday, <a href="https://fansided.com/2023/06/05/rangers-concede-defeat-jacob-degrom-injury-status/">the Rangers placed deGrom on the 60-day injured list</a> with right elbow inflammation that forced him from his Apr. 28 start against the New York Yankees. The team would send him to undergo another MRI on Tuesday to see how he was progressing.Unfortunately for deGrom, his debut season with the Rangers is officially over. As first reported by Evan Grant of the Dallas Morning News, deGrom is set to undergo Tommy John surgery to repair a tear in his UCL. The full extent of the tear won’t be known until he undergoes surgery, which is scheduled for next week.To clarify: Full extent of surgery will be determined once Dr Keith Meister gets inside of elbow. For now: Ligament repair. That doesn’t rule out something like an internal brace. Either way: Out at least 12 months <a href="https://t.co/Or6mRXmbOZ">https://t.co/Or6mRXmbOZ</a>— Evan Grant (@Evan_P_Grant) <a href="https://twitter.com/Evan_P_Grant/status/1666185627019116544?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 6, 2023</a>Jacob deGrom’s debut season with Rangers is over, as he’s set to undergo Tommy John surgeryIt has been a rough couple of years for deGrom. He missed the second half of the 2021 season with the Mets due to right elbow inflammation. Then in 2022, deGrom missed the start of the campaign due to a stress reaction of his right scapula.Unfortunately, the injuries carried over into his first year with Texas. At the start of spring training, deGrom was limited with left-side tightness. Then, in mid-April, he left a start against the Kansas City Royals due to right wrist soreness. His latest injury scare turned out to be one that would end his season after just six starts.deGrom has recorded a 2.67 ERA, a 0.758 WHIP, 45 strikeouts, and four walks in 30.1 innings.The Rangers have been performing well without deGrom, but this is the worst news they could have gotten. deGrom was supposed to play a pivotal role in the team making it back to the postseason for the first time since 2016. Now, he will be out until midway through the 2024 season. <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/rangers-jacob-degrom-tommy-john-worst-case/">Latest Jacob deGrom injury update is worst-case scenario for Rangers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://us.yorba.org/rangers-jacob-degrom-tommy-john-worst-case/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Braves rumors: 3 superstar pitcher trades to fix the issue, 2 budget options to help</title>
		<link>http://us.yorba.org/braves-trade-rumors-superstars-budget/</link>
					<comments>http://us.yorba.org/braves-trade-rumors-superstars-budget/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[usyorba]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:46:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Braves]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[budget]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fix]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[issue]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[options]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pitcher]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[rumors]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[superstar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[trades]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://us.yorba.org/?p=65</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shane Bieber, Cleveland Guardians. (Photo by Ron Schwane/Getty Images)The Atlanta Braves are still trying to find answers for the rotation and the trade market could heat up with superstars and budget options...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/braves-trade-rumors-superstars-budget/">Braves rumors: 3 superstar pitcher trades to fix the issue, 2 budget options to help</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shane Bieber, Cleveland Guardians. (Photo by Ron Schwane/Getty Images)The Atlanta Braves are still trying to find answers for the rotation and the trade market could heat up with superstars and budget options both available.It’s frankly somewhat remarkable that the <a href="https://fansided.com/2023/06/06/braves-rumors-soroka-mets-contract/">Atlanta Braves</a> have been as dominant in the 2023 season given the issues they’ve had with pitching, specifically the rotation as the bullpen has started to round into form.Injuries to Max Fried, Kyle Wright and Ian Anderson have put them behind the 8-ball and manager Brian Snitker has left no stone unturned trying to find replacements to help them through this time. But Michael Soroka was optioned back to Triple-A after two up-and-down starts, Dylan Dodd has been inconsistent as well, and the bullpen games yielded unkind results.With Fried being moved to the 60-day IL, a lack of faith in Soroka after his first two starts, and a potential reluctance to elevate 20-year-old AJ Smith-Shawver into a starting role so soon after he started the season in Single-A, it might be time for Alex Anthopoulos and the Braves to finally get active on the trade market.But in that light, do the <a href="https://fansided.com/2023/06/04/braves-rumors-brewers-trade-targets/">Atlanta Braves</a> target superstars in a trade to possibly fix the issue long term, or rather look to more budget-friendly options that can be helpful to get through this season? Let’s take a look at both with three stars and two budget options the Braves could trade for.Braves trade rumors: 3 superstars to fix pitching issues, 2 budget options5. Shane Bieber would be a Cy Young-caliber fix for the Braves long termBubbling under the surface in Cleveland has been the possibility that the Guardians would move former Cy Young winner Shane Bieber at the MLB Trade Deadline. He’s in the next to last year of club control before he’ll be a free agent and extension talks have not been particularly fruitful.If the Guardians are going to trade Bieber, though, that’s a market that the <a href="https://fansided.com/2023/06/03/braves-rumors-3-trades-2-avoid/">Atlanta Braves</a> would be completely foolish to not sniff around in.Bieber hasn’t been as dominant this season as in some year’s past, but he’s still been a high-end starting pitcher. Through 12 starts, the 28-year-old has posted a 3.72 ERA with a 1.29 WHIP. A minor issue early on has been a decline in his K/BB ration to 2.5, well below his career-worst of 4.1 for a season. But that has started to rebound.You also simply can’t forget how unhittable he’s been at times, most notably in the shortened 2020 season when he won the AL Cy Young in which he posted an absurd 1.63 ERA and 0.87 WHIP over 12 starts with Cleveland.Anthopoulous and the Braves have made their bones about trading for guys at the end of club control and then locking them up on extensions. If that’s the route that they choose to go to address the issues with the rotation, Bieber is about as good of an option as you could imagine.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/braves-trade-rumors-superstars-budget/">Braves rumors: 3 superstar pitcher trades to fix the issue, 2 budget options to help</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://us.yorba.org/braves-trade-rumors-superstars-budget/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brian Snitker wisely reinserts Marcell Ozuna into lineup after benching</title>
		<link>http://us.yorba.org/brian-snitker-marcell-ozuna-reinserted-braves-lineup/</link>
					<comments>http://us.yorba.org/brian-snitker-marcell-ozuna-reinserted-braves-lineup/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[usyorba]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:23:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[benching]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brian]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[lineup]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marcell]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ozuna]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[reinserts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Snitker]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[wisely]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://us.yorba.org/?p=56</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Atlanta Braves manager Brian Snitker made the right call by reinserting Marcell Ozuna into the starting lineup after his benching on Sunday.It took two days, but Marcell Ozuna will be back in...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/brian-snitker-marcell-ozuna-reinserted-braves-lineup/">Brian Snitker wisely reinserts Marcell Ozuna into lineup after benching</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p> Atlanta Braves manager Brian Snitker made the right call by reinserting Marcell Ozuna into the starting lineup after his benching on Sunday.It took two days, but Marcell Ozuna will be back in the starting lineup for the <a href="http://fansided.com/mlb/mlb-teams/atlanta-braves">Atlanta Braves</a> vs. the <a href="http://fansided.com/mlb/mlb-teams/new-york-mets">New York Mets</a> after getting benched in Sunday’s series finale vs. the <a href="http://fansided.com/mlb/mlb-teams/arizona-diamondbacks">Arizona Diamondbacks</a>.Braves skipper Brian Snitker pulled the controversial designated hitter from the game in favor of backstop Sean Murphy. This had everything to do with Ozuna not hustling out of the box on what was a 415-foot single to deep centerfield. Ozuna thought he parked one, but because he wasn’t running hard, he was unable to get extra bases on a critical play in a crucial game vs. an NL foe.After an off-day, Snitker did the right thing by penciling Ozuna into the starting lineup on Tuesday.Ozuna will bat seventh as the Atlanta DH in Game 1 of their home series vs. the arch rival Mets.Atlanta Braves: Brian Snitker made right call in starting Marcell Ozuna TuesdayLook. This has nothing to do with how Ozuna does at the plate in this game, or in this series, for that matter. It’s about a manager and one of his players being on the same page in doing whatever is necessary to win games. Snitker had to pull Ozuna from the game, and Ozuna knew it. Bobby Cox did this to Andruw Jones back in the day. It doesn’t happen often, but these things do happen.We’re talking about professionals who play and manage a children’s game for a living. Nothing is given here, it is earned. Surely, Ozuna feels terrible about not playing up to his standard in that moment in Phoenix. However, I think it’s great that they can move forward in this and try to win anyway. The best part is Ozuna has hit very well at the plate for the better part of five weeks now.Overall, you had to have been out of your gourd to think Snitker was going to permanently bench Ozuna for marveling at his long single. You probably got chastised at some point playing youth baseball or softball on a similar play. We are all human! Above all else, why would Snitker keep one of <a href="http://fansided.com/mlb">MLB</a>‘s most dangerous right-handed hitters on the bench when his OPS of late is 1.000-plus?The Mets are in town, so nothing else matters. Focus all of your attention to beat the hated Mets! </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/brian-snitker-marcell-ozuna-reinserted-braves-lineup/">Brian Snitker wisely reinserts Marcell Ozuna into lineup after benching</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://us.yorba.org/brian-snitker-marcell-ozuna-reinserted-braves-lineup/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>NBA rumors: Kyrie Irving claims LeBron reports weren’t a ploy to get to LA</title>
		<link>http://us.yorba.org/nba-rumors-kyrie-irving-lebron-trade-lakers/</link>
					<comments>http://us.yorba.org/nba-rumors-kyrie-irving-lebron-trade-lakers/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[usyorba]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:18:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[claims]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Irving]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kyrie]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LeBron]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NBA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ploy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[rumors]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[werent]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://us.yorba.org/?p=41</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Despite rampant speculation suggesting otherwise, Kyrie Irving is apparently content to re-sign with the Dallas Mavericks. Kyrie Irving has been tied to LeBron James and the Los Angeles Lakers since before the trade...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/nba-rumors-kyrie-irving-lebron-trade-lakers/">NBA rumors: Kyrie Irving claims LeBron reports weren’t a ploy to get to LA</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p> Despite rampant speculation suggesting otherwise, Kyrie Irving is apparently content to re-sign with the Dallas Mavericks. Kyrie Irving has been tied to LeBron James and the <a href="https://fansided.com/nba/nba-teams/los-angeles-lakers/">Los Angeles Lakers</a> since before the trade deadline last season. The disgruntled star was traded from Brooklyn to Dallas in the final year of an expiring contract and, to add fuel to the fire of speculation, the <a href="https://fansided.com/nba/nba-teams/dallas-mavericks/">Mavs</a> missed the playoffs despite a statistically fruitful partnership between Kyrie and Luka Doncic.Irving then went on to attend multiple Lakers playoff games, leading some to believe he was angling to get in the good graces of LeBron and the Lakers’ front office. Irving famously demanded a trade away from LeBron in Cleveland but has since seen the error in his ways.<a href="https://marcstein.substack.com/p/lebron-and-the-mavericks?r=o66it&amp;utm_campaign=post&amp;utm_medium=email" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">New reporting from NBA insider Marc Stein</a>, however, paints a different picture of Irving’s upcoming free agency.Kyrie Irving wants to re-sign with the Dallas Mavericks“Two sources close to the process insisted Monday that Irving has consistently expressed a desire to remain a Maverick and actually wants to shut down the notion that he’s angling to get to L.A.”That kind of sentiment will come as a surprise to many, especially those among the LA faithful who were hoping for Kyrie to push the Lakers over the finish line. That said, the Mavs have every financial advantage to keep Irving. Meanwhile, the Lakers are not interested in the idea of reuniting LeBron with his former co-champion, <a href="https://theathletic.com/4582508/2023/06/05/kyrie-lebron-mavericks-lakers/?source=emp_shared_article" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">according to Jovan Buha of The Athletic</a>.This feels like a perfect storm of those two facts: Irving can get the most money from Dallas and the Lakers don’t want him or the headache he traditionally brings with him. Irving probably enjoys playing with Luka Doncic too. Just because last season ended poorly doesn’t mean 2023-24 will end the same way.Irving and Doncic form arguably the most skilled, potent guard duo in the NBA. Irving is <a href="https://fansided.com/2023/06/05/kyrie-irving-lebron-trade-twitter/">openly recruiting LeBron to Dallas</a>, to really drive home his desire to stick around. The logistics of that hypothetical transaction are <a href="https://fansided.com/2023/06/06/5-assets-mavericks-acquire-lebron-james/">borderline unfathomable</a>, but hey — it’s a nice thought.Irving and LeBron have progressed past the conflict that once mired their relationship and Irving evidently has a place where he’s happy playing basketball. This feels like a win all around. Don’t expect Irving and James to team up any time soon, but get excited for the next year-plus of Irving and Luka dancing on hapless defenders. </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/nba-rumors-kyrie-irving-lebron-trade-lakers/">NBA rumors: Kyrie Irving claims LeBron reports weren’t a ploy to get to LA</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://us.yorba.org/nba-rumors-kyrie-irving-lebron-trade-lakers/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Saints biggest offensive weapon finally appears to be fully healthy</title>
		<link>http://us.yorba.org/saints-michael-thomas-health/</link>
					<comments>http://us.yorba.org/saints-michael-thomas-health/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[usyorba]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:11:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[appears]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[biggest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[finally]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fully]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[healthy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[offensive]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Saints]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[weapon]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://us.yorba.org/?p=32</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The New Orleans Saints have a new starting quarterback. It also appears that wide receiver  Michael Thomas is ready to make his presence felt again.There was nothing but positives when it came...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/saints-michael-thomas-health/">Saints biggest offensive weapon finally appears to be fully healthy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p> The New Orleans Saints have a new starting quarterback. It also appears that wide receiver  Michael Thomas is ready to make his presence felt again.There was nothing but positives when it came to the first of the <a href="https://fullpresscoverage.com/2023/05/25/biggest-remaining-question-for-each-nfc-south-team/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">New Orleans Saints</a> second-round picks in 2016. One-time Ohio State wide receiver Michael Thomas caught 92 passes for 1,137 yards and nine scores.Things would only get better for the former Buckeye. His number would increase with each passing year. Thomas totaled 104, 125, and an NFL-record 149 receptions, respectively, over the next three seasons. Those grabs added up to 1,245, 1,405, and a league-high 1,725 yards.These are amazing totals. In his first four seasons combined, Thomas amassed 470 catches for 5,512 yards and 32 touchdowns. There would be three straight Pro Bowl invitations from 2017-19. The reliable wideout earned All-Pro honors in 2018 and ’19, and that latter year would also result in the Saints’ star being named the NFL Offensive Player of the Year.Then came the injury bug. It bit Thomas in numerous ways. He played only seven games in 2020 and missed all of 2021 due to an ankle problem. He got off to a solid start this past season, catching 16 passes for 171 yards and three scores in the club’s first three contests. However, he would not play in another game for the remainder of the season.Now it’s 2023 and there seems to be optimism surrounding the 30-year-old wideout.Saints WR Michael Thomas said he will be ready for training camp &#8220;Day 1, full speed.&#8221; Said he&#8217;ll be back to form &#8220;just like everyone’s used to.&#8221;— Mike Triplett (@MikeTriplett) <a href="https://twitter.com/MikeTriplett/status/1666143548171776007?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 6, 2023</a>The Saints are coming off a<a href="https://fansided.com/2023/04/30/nfl-power-rankings-2023-post-nfl-draft/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">highly-disappointing 7-10 campaign</a>, the team’s first losing season since 2016. The offense was mediocre at best and Dennis Allen’s club turned over the ball 25 times. The franchise <a href="https://fullpresscoverage.com/2023/03/21/nfl-2023-key-comings-and-goings-as-of-june-5/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">signed former Raiders’ signal-caller Derek Carr </a>this offseason after he was cut loose by Las Vegas.A healthy Thomas is huge news <a href="https://www.ourlads.com/nfldepthcharts/depthchart/NO" target="_blank" rel="noopener">for a wide receiving corps</a> that already includes veteran Tre’Quan Smith as well as another former Buckeye in 2022 first-round pick <a href="https://fansided.com/2022/11/20/chris-olave-saints-week-11/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Chris Olave</a>. The latter led the team this past season with 72 catches and 1,042 receiving yards, totaling four touchdowns.If Thomas can recapture any of that former All-Pro form, the Saints’ offense could rebound from a problem-plagued showing. <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script><br /></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/saints-michael-thomas-health/">Saints biggest offensive weapon finally appears to be fully healthy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://us.yorba.org/saints-michael-thomas-health/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Aaron Rodgers has some limits at New York Jets offseason workouts</title>
		<link>http://us.yorba.org/aaron-rodgers-has-some-limits-at-new-york-jets-offseason-workouts/</link>
					<comments>http://us.yorba.org/aaron-rodgers-has-some-limits-at-new-york-jets-offseason-workouts/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[usyorba]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:09:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aaron]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[limits]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[offseason]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rodgers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[workouts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[York]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://us.yorba.org/?p=29</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New York Jets quarterback Aaron Rodgers was active at Tuesday’s offseason workouts, but the team won’t let him participate in one drill in particular.The New York Jets were feeling good after the...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/aaron-rodgers-has-some-limits-at-new-york-jets-offseason-workouts/">Aaron Rodgers has some limits at New York Jets offseason workouts</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p> New York Jets quarterback Aaron Rodgers was active at Tuesday’s offseason workouts, but the team won’t let him participate in one drill in particular.The <a href="https://fansided.com/nfl/teams/new-york-jets/">New York Jets</a> were feeling good after the team made the blockbuster trade for four-time NFL MVP Aaron Rodgers to be their starting quarterback. With a strong option under center, the Jets have huge aspirations heading into the season. But Jets fans wondered when the good vibes would end. Well, there was a pause on May 24 when Rodgers strained his calf. Since Rodgers had been limited during organized team activities.On Tuesday, Jets head coach Robert Saleh revealed that Rodgers will do everything in practice besides participate in 11-on-11 drills. The reason behind it, per Saleh, is that they didn’t want any other player near Rodgers’ legs.Robert Saleh says Aaron Rodgers will do everything today except for 11-on-11. The <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Jets?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Jets</a> don’t want anyone by his legs.— Connor Hughes (@Connor_J_Hughes) <a href="https://twitter.com/Connor_J_Hughes/status/1666094145012899840?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 6, 2023</a>Aaron Rodgers active in June 6 workouts, but did not participate in 11-on-11 drillsYes, it’s organized team activities, but hearing that Rodgers is progressing from his calf injury has to be great news for them. However, they just want to hear that he will be good to go for the start of the regular season, in which they face the Buffalo Bills on Monday Night Football.The Jets have just two more practices for organized team activities on June 8 and 9. The team was supposed to have mandatory minicamp from June 13-15, but <a href="https://www.sny.tv/articles/robert-saleh-why-jets-won-t-be-holding-mandatory-minicamp-2023">Saleh announced that they were canceled</a>. The reasoning behind the decision is that the Jets are starting training camp a week earlier than other teams because they will be participating in this year’s Hall of Fame Game.No official start date for training camp has been announced as of this writing.Rodgers is coming off of a 2022 season in which he threw for 3,695 yards, 26 touchdowns, and 12 interceptions while completing 64.6 percent of his passes.This upcoming season, he will have some familiar faces to target like Allen Lazard and Randall Cobb, and some new faces like Garrett Wilson and Mecole Hardman. Fans will continue to follow updates in the final two days of OTAs. <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script><br /></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/aaron-rodgers-has-some-limits-at-new-york-jets-offseason-workouts/">Aaron Rodgers has some limits at New York Jets offseason workouts</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://us.yorba.org/aaron-rodgers-has-some-limits-at-new-york-jets-offseason-workouts/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
