<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Rodgers Archives - Yorba Foundation</title>
	<atom:link href="http://us.yorba.org/tag/rodgers/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://us.yorba.org/tag/rodgers/</link>
	<description>USA</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:09:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Aaron Rodgers has some limits at New York Jets offseason workouts</title>
		<link>http://us.yorba.org/aaron-rodgers-has-some-limits-at-new-york-jets-offseason-workouts/</link>
					<comments>http://us.yorba.org/aaron-rodgers-has-some-limits-at-new-york-jets-offseason-workouts/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[usyorba]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:09:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aaron]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[limits]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[offseason]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rodgers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[workouts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[York]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://us.yorba.org/?p=29</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New York Jets quarterback Aaron Rodgers was active at Tuesday’s offseason workouts, but the team won’t let him participate in one drill in particular.The New York Jets were feeling good after the...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/aaron-rodgers-has-some-limits-at-new-york-jets-offseason-workouts/">Aaron Rodgers has some limits at New York Jets offseason workouts</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p> New York Jets quarterback Aaron Rodgers was active at Tuesday’s offseason workouts, but the team won’t let him participate in one drill in particular.The <a href="https://fansided.com/nfl/teams/new-york-jets/">New York Jets</a> were feeling good after the team made the blockbuster trade for four-time NFL MVP Aaron Rodgers to be their starting quarterback. With a strong option under center, the Jets have huge aspirations heading into the season. But Jets fans wondered when the good vibes would end. Well, there was a pause on May 24 when Rodgers strained his calf. Since Rodgers had been limited during organized team activities.On Tuesday, Jets head coach Robert Saleh revealed that Rodgers will do everything in practice besides participate in 11-on-11 drills. The reason behind it, per Saleh, is that they didn’t want any other player near Rodgers’ legs.Robert Saleh says Aaron Rodgers will do everything today except for 11-on-11. The <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Jets?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Jets</a> don’t want anyone by his legs.— Connor Hughes (@Connor_J_Hughes) <a href="https://twitter.com/Connor_J_Hughes/status/1666094145012899840?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 6, 2023</a>Aaron Rodgers active in June 6 workouts, but did not participate in 11-on-11 drillsYes, it’s organized team activities, but hearing that Rodgers is progressing from his calf injury has to be great news for them. However, they just want to hear that he will be good to go for the start of the regular season, in which they face the Buffalo Bills on Monday Night Football.The Jets have just two more practices for organized team activities on June 8 and 9. The team was supposed to have mandatory minicamp from June 13-15, but <a href="https://www.sny.tv/articles/robert-saleh-why-jets-won-t-be-holding-mandatory-minicamp-2023">Saleh announced that they were canceled</a>. The reasoning behind the decision is that the Jets are starting training camp a week earlier than other teams because they will be participating in this year’s Hall of Fame Game.No official start date for training camp has been announced as of this writing.Rodgers is coming off of a 2022 season in which he threw for 3,695 yards, 26 touchdowns, and 12 interceptions while completing 64.6 percent of his passes.This upcoming season, he will have some familiar faces to target like Allen Lazard and Randall Cobb, and some new faces like Garrett Wilson and Mecole Hardman. Fans will continue to follow updates in the final two days of OTAs. <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script><br /></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/aaron-rodgers-has-some-limits-at-new-york-jets-offseason-workouts/">Aaron Rodgers has some limits at New York Jets offseason workouts</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://us.yorba.org/aaron-rodgers-has-some-limits-at-new-york-jets-offseason-workouts/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
