<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Lincoln Archives - Yorba Foundation</title>
	<atom:link href="http://us.yorba.org/tag/lincoln/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://us.yorba.org/tag/lincoln/</link>
	<description>USA</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:20:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Lincoln Lawyer Season 2 Split In 2 Parts, Release Date, &#038; New Images Revealed</title>
		<link>http://us.yorba.org/lincoln-lawyer-season-2-images-release-date/</link>
					<comments>http://us.yorba.org/lincoln-lawyer-season-2-images-release-date/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[usyorba]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:20:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Movie]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[amp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Date]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Images]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lawyer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lincoln]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Parts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Revealed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Season]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Split]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://us.yorba.org/?p=44</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Lincoln Lawyer season 2 announces a release schedule and unveils new images. Based on the book series of the same name by Michael Connelly, which was previously adapted into the 2011...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/lincoln-lawyer-season-2-images-release-date/">Lincoln Lawyer Season 2 Split In 2 Parts, Release Date, &amp; New Images Revealed</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img decoding="async" src="https://static1.srcdn.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/the-lincoln-lawyer-season-2-manuel-garcia-rulfo-neve-campbell.jpeg" /><br />
<a href="https://screenrant.com/tag/the-lincoln-lawyer/">The Lincoln Lawyer</a> season 2 announces a release schedule and unveils new images. Based on the book series of the same name by Michael Connelly, which was previously adapted into the 2011 movie staring Matthew McConaughey, the Netflix legal drama follows Manuel Garcia-Rulfo as Mickey Haller, a criminal-defense lawyer who works out of his titular vehicle rather than a traditional office. <a href="https://screenrant.com/lincoln-lawyer-show-cast-characters-book-explained/">The Lincoln Lawyer cast</a> also includes Neve Campbell, Becki Newton, Jazz Raycole, Angus Sampson, and Christopher Gorham.<br />
SCREENRANT VIDEO OF THE DAYSCROLL TO CONTINUE WITH CONTENT</p>
<p>Today, Netflix (via <a href="https://tvline.com/2023/06/06/lincoln-lawyer-season-2-release-date-photos-netflix/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">TVLine</a>) unveiled first-look photos for <a href="https://screenrant.com/lincoln-lawyer-season-2-updates-story-news/">The Lincoln Lawyer season 2</a>. The images show Mickey alongside his first ex-wife and Deputy District Attorney Maggie (played by Campbell) and two new characters – a prosecutor named Andrea Freeman (Yaya DaCosta) and Lisa Trammell (Lana Parrilla), a chef accused of murdering a real estate developer. Mickey&#8217;s personal driver Izzy Letts (Jazz Raycole) and second ex-wife and legal aid Lorna Crane (Becki Newton) are also showcased. Check out the images below:</p>
<p>In addition to the first-look photos, a release schedule was also announced. The Lincoln Lawyer season 2, part 1 is set to hit Netflix on July 6 with the second half arriving a month later on August 3.</p>
<p> What To Expect From The Lincoln Lawyer Season 2 </p>
<p>Skipping over the third, <a href="https://screenrant.com/lincoln-lawyer-season-2-netflix-which-book/">The Lincoln Lawyer season 2 is based on the fourth book</a> in Connelly&#8217;s series titled The Fifth Witness, which finds Mickey defending Lisa after she is suspected of murdering a wealthy real estate developer. The second season starts six months after the conclusion of the Trevor Elliot case from season 1 as Mickey is still riding high off winning the high-profile case before he is thrust into a new one. Mickey&#8217;s new case in season 2 will be complicated by his personal connection to it since he becomes emotionally attached to Lisa before defending her.</p>
<p>Related: <a href="https://screenrant.com/lincoln-lawyer-netflix-skip-book-3-good/">Why The Lincoln Lawyer Has To Skip Book 3 (&amp; Why It Should Do It Later)</a></p>
<p>Though the second season will introduce a new high-profile case for Mickey, it won&#8217;t forget about the lingering mystery involving the killer with the tattoo on his forearm. By continuing this overarching storyline from season 1 while also having Mickey take on new cases both big and small, The Lincoln Lawyer season 2 should strike a nice balance of continuing and new storylines. This should attract both returning and new audiences when the legal drama returns to Netflix this summer.</p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://tvline.com/2023/06/06/lincoln-lawyer-season-2-release-date-photos-netflix/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">TVLine</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/lincoln-lawyer-season-2-images-release-date/">Lincoln Lawyer Season 2 Split In 2 Parts, Release Date, &amp; New Images Revealed</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://us.yorba.org/lincoln-lawyer-season-2-images-release-date/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
