<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>amp Archives - Yorba Foundation</title>
	<atom:link href="http://us.yorba.org/tag/amp/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://us.yorba.org/tag/amp/</link>
	<description>USA</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:33:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Joe Giudice Claims RHONJ Stars Were Involved With Calling Feds On Him &#038; Teresa</title>
		<link>http://us.yorba.org/real-housewives-of-new-jersey-joe-giudice-fbi/</link>
					<comments>http://us.yorba.org/real-housewives-of-new-jersey-joe-giudice-fbi/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[usyorba]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:33:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Movie]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[amp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Calling]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[claims]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feds]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Giudice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Involved]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Joe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[RHONJ]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stars]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teresa]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://us.yorba.org/?p=62</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The drama surrounding who called the FBI on The Real Housewives of New Jersey&#8216;s Joe and Teresa Giudice continues, as the former is putting blame on Melissa and Joe Gorga for the...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/real-housewives-of-new-jersey-joe-giudice-fbi/">Joe Giudice Claims RHONJ Stars Were Involved With Calling Feds On Him &amp; Teresa</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img decoding="async" src="https://static1.srcdn.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/sin-ti-tulo-1-9-2.jpg" /><br />
The drama surrounding who called the FBI on <a href="https://screenrant.com/tag/the-real-housewives-of-new-jersey/">The Real Housewives of New Jersey</a>&#8216;s Joe and Teresa Giudice continues, as the former is putting blame on Melissa and Joe Gorga for the whole ordeal. The speculation started up again recently when <a href="https://screenrant.com/real-housewives-of-new-jersey-season-13-reunion-trailer/">Teresa made the bold accusation</a> during the RHONJ season 13 reunion that Melissa turned her and her then-husband in. The now-former couple was sent to prison&#8211;over three years for Joe Giudice and less than one year for Teresa&#8211;for tax and bank fraud, among other charges. They ended up serving their respective sentences at separate times so that one of the parents could always be with their children.<br />
SCREENRANT VIDEO OF THE DAYSCROLL TO CONTINUE WITH CONTENT</p>
<p>Teresa and Joe Giudice&#8217;s prison sentences are well behind them now, but the drama surrounding how they got there hasn&#8217;t ended. Following Teresa&#8217;s recent comments at the RHONJ season 13 reunion, Joe Giudice echoed those claims while appearing on the <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/juicy-joe-giudice-on-rhonj-past-present-who-called/id1496557812?i=1000615693123" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Behind The Velvet Rope</a> podcast. &#8220;I think Melissa and Joe were involved&#8221; in alerting the FBI. He noted that <a href="https://screenrant.com/real-housewives-new-jersey-melissa-joe-gorga-relationship/">RHONJ&#8217;s Melissa and Joe Gorga</a> were apparently &#8220;good friends&#8221; with his &#8220;ex-partner&#8217;s attorneys, which went to the feds.&#8221;</p>
<p> Joe Giudice Claims Former FBI Agent Told Him About Melissa &amp; Joe Gorga </p>
<p>This alone is a giant accusation to make, but <a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/CsXjYcmgKIo/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Joe Giudice</a> also alleged that he was told this information from a man who used to work at the FBI. This is why he believes the Gorgas turning them in is a &#8220;fact.&#8221; He concluded, &#8220;[Melissa and Joe] went to the feds to feed them all this information. Yeah, I might&#8217;ve cheated on some things, my tax returns, who didn&#8217;t?&#8221; During the same podcast discussion, Joe Giudice continuously slammed Melissa and Joe Gorga and claimed that they should be thanking him since they got paid for a RHONJ spin-off called Teresa Checks In, which revolved around Teresa&#8217;s time behind bars.</p>
<p>Aside from the blame game at the heart of this accusation, it appears that Joe Giudice believes someone turning him in to the FBI is worse than the actual crime he committed. By saying, &#8220;Who didn&#8217;t?&#8221; he&#8217;s dismissing his tax fraud by insinuating lots of other people do it, so it&#8217;s, therefore, not a big deal to him. Considering this matter involves breaking the law, it definitely is a big deal. Obviously, he would love to know who turned him in since it affects him and his whole family. But caring more about the informants than feeling remorse for the crimes that were committed isn&#8217;t a great position to have.</p>
<p>Related: <a href="https://screenrant.com/rhonj-all-times-joe-gorga-fought-joe-giudice/">RHONJ: All The Times Joe Gorga Has Fought With Joe Giudice</a></p>
<p>The feud between Teresa and the Gorgas is clearly not ending anytime soon. If anything, the recent RHONJ season 13 reunion and Joe Giudice&#8217;s podcast comments proved that things are ramping up even more. Caroline Manzo recently claimed she knows who called the FBI on the Giudices but refused to divulge any names, so it&#8217;s left up to those at the center of the scandal to try to fill in the gaps with various allegations, regardless of whether they&#8217;re true or not. It&#8217;s not surprising they&#8217;re putting the blame on the Gorgas, but it&#8217;s unclear if the absolute truth will ever come out to either support or refute these allegations.</p>
<p>The Real Housewives of New Jersey airs Tuesdays at 8 p.m. EDT on Bravo.</p>
<p>Sources: <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/juicy-joe-giudice-on-rhonj-past-present-who-called/id1496557812?i=1000615693123" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Behind The Velvet Rope</a>/Apple Podcasts, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/CsXjYcmgKIo/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Joe Gorga</a>/Instagram</p>
<p> <script async defer src="https://platform.instagram.com/en_US/embeds.js"></script></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/real-housewives-of-new-jersey-joe-giudice-fbi/">Joe Giudice Claims RHONJ Stars Were Involved With Calling Feds On Him &amp; Teresa</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://us.yorba.org/real-housewives-of-new-jersey-joe-giudice-fbi/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lincoln Lawyer Season 2 Split In 2 Parts, Release Date, &#038; New Images Revealed</title>
		<link>http://us.yorba.org/lincoln-lawyer-season-2-images-release-date/</link>
					<comments>http://us.yorba.org/lincoln-lawyer-season-2-images-release-date/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[usyorba]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:20:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Movie]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[amp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Date]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Images]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lawyer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lincoln]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Parts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Release]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Revealed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Season]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Split]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://us.yorba.org/?p=44</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Lincoln Lawyer season 2 announces a release schedule and unveils new images. Based on the book series of the same name by Michael Connelly, which was previously adapted into the 2011...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/lincoln-lawyer-season-2-images-release-date/">Lincoln Lawyer Season 2 Split In 2 Parts, Release Date, &amp; New Images Revealed</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img decoding="async" src="https://static1.srcdn.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/the-lincoln-lawyer-season-2-manuel-garcia-rulfo-neve-campbell.jpeg" /><br />
<a href="https://screenrant.com/tag/the-lincoln-lawyer/">The Lincoln Lawyer</a> season 2 announces a release schedule and unveils new images. Based on the book series of the same name by Michael Connelly, which was previously adapted into the 2011 movie staring Matthew McConaughey, the Netflix legal drama follows Manuel Garcia-Rulfo as Mickey Haller, a criminal-defense lawyer who works out of his titular vehicle rather than a traditional office. <a href="https://screenrant.com/lincoln-lawyer-show-cast-characters-book-explained/">The Lincoln Lawyer cast</a> also includes Neve Campbell, Becki Newton, Jazz Raycole, Angus Sampson, and Christopher Gorham.<br />
SCREENRANT VIDEO OF THE DAYSCROLL TO CONTINUE WITH CONTENT</p>
<p>Today, Netflix (via <a href="https://tvline.com/2023/06/06/lincoln-lawyer-season-2-release-date-photos-netflix/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">TVLine</a>) unveiled first-look photos for <a href="https://screenrant.com/lincoln-lawyer-season-2-updates-story-news/">The Lincoln Lawyer season 2</a>. The images show Mickey alongside his first ex-wife and Deputy District Attorney Maggie (played by Campbell) and two new characters – a prosecutor named Andrea Freeman (Yaya DaCosta) and Lisa Trammell (Lana Parrilla), a chef accused of murdering a real estate developer. Mickey&#8217;s personal driver Izzy Letts (Jazz Raycole) and second ex-wife and legal aid Lorna Crane (Becki Newton) are also showcased. Check out the images below:</p>
<p>In addition to the first-look photos, a release schedule was also announced. The Lincoln Lawyer season 2, part 1 is set to hit Netflix on July 6 with the second half arriving a month later on August 3.</p>
<p> What To Expect From The Lincoln Lawyer Season 2 </p>
<p>Skipping over the third, <a href="https://screenrant.com/lincoln-lawyer-season-2-netflix-which-book/">The Lincoln Lawyer season 2 is based on the fourth book</a> in Connelly&#8217;s series titled The Fifth Witness, which finds Mickey defending Lisa after she is suspected of murdering a wealthy real estate developer. The second season starts six months after the conclusion of the Trevor Elliot case from season 1 as Mickey is still riding high off winning the high-profile case before he is thrust into a new one. Mickey&#8217;s new case in season 2 will be complicated by his personal connection to it since he becomes emotionally attached to Lisa before defending her.</p>
<p>Related: <a href="https://screenrant.com/lincoln-lawyer-netflix-skip-book-3-good/">Why The Lincoln Lawyer Has To Skip Book 3 (&amp; Why It Should Do It Later)</a></p>
<p>Though the second season will introduce a new high-profile case for Mickey, it won&#8217;t forget about the lingering mystery involving the killer with the tattoo on his forearm. By continuing this overarching storyline from season 1 while also having Mickey take on new cases both big and small, The Lincoln Lawyer season 2 should strike a nice balance of continuing and new storylines. This should attract both returning and new audiences when the legal drama returns to Netflix this summer.</p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://tvline.com/2023/06/06/lincoln-lawyer-season-2-release-date-photos-netflix/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">TVLine</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/lincoln-lawyer-season-2-images-release-date/">Lincoln Lawyer Season 2 Split In 2 Parts, Release Date, &amp; New Images Revealed</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://us.yorba.org/lincoln-lawyer-season-2-images-release-date/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
