<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>mustsee Archives - Yorba Foundation</title>
	<atom:link href="http://us.yorba.org/tag/mustsee/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://us.yorba.org/tag/mustsee/</link>
	<description>USA</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:53:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>WNBA Week Three: 3 must-see matchups this week</title>
		<link>http://us.yorba.org/wnba-power-rankings-3-best-games-week-3/</link>
					<comments>http://us.yorba.org/wnba-power-rankings-3-best-games-week-3/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[usyorba]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:53:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[matchups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mustsee]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Week]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[WNBA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://us.yorba.org/?p=92</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The WNBA has a full slate of games this week. Which matchups should be at the top of your viewing list?The WNBA season is in full swing and entering week three of...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/wnba-power-rankings-3-best-games-week-3/">WNBA Week Three: 3 must-see matchups this week</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p> The WNBA has a full slate of games this week. Which matchups should be at the top of your viewing list?The <a href="http://fansided.com/wnba/">WNBA</a> season is in full swing and entering week three of action. Awards races are starting to shape up. All-Star <a href="https://twitter.com/alfcorriette/status/1665781517925187585">voting starts tomorrow</a>.With storylines developing across the league, it can be overwhelming to keep up with what’s going on where. With consistent schedule overlap, it can be even more difficult choosing which games to watch.Allow us to help you decide. Here are three must-see games from this week’s WNBA slate.WNBA must-see games this week, June 5-June 12Las Vegas Aces at Connecticut Sun, June 6, 7 p.m. ESTWhere to watch: WNBA League Pass, NBC Sports Boston, Fox 5, SSSENA rematch of last year’s Finals, this might be the most anticipated game of the year, so far. The best part? These two teams also play on Thursday, Jun 8.Once again, this is matchup of the best two teams in the league. The Aces are the lone undefeated team remaining, while the Sun are right behind them at 6-1. The game features <a href="https://fansided.com/2023/06/06/wnba-mvp-ladder-alyssa-thomas-jackie-young/">two current MVP candidates</a> and will be a fun battle of styles. The Aces lead the league in field goal percentage, and hold their opponents to the lowest shooting percentage. The Sun hold opponents to the worst three-point shooting percentage, and have the third-best scoring defense in the league.Despite the familiarity, neither team is the same as the last time they met. The Sun have a new coach, system, and largely new roster. The Aces have much-improved depth, and an improved starting five (shoutout to Candace Parker).Chicago Sky at Los Angeles Sparks, June 9, 10 p.m. ESTWhere to watch: IonTV, WNBA League PassA battle of two scrappy teams who are outperforming expectations, this one should be a fun watch. Plus, it will be Azurá Stevens’ first game against her former team.ROSTER UPDATE: The Los Angeles Sparks announced today that Azurá Stevens has been activated ahead of Tuesday’s game against the Seattle Storm. Full Release: <a href="https://t.co/OiU9fxrzgm">https://t.co/OiU9fxrzgm</a>— LA Sparks PR (@LASparksPR) <a href="https://twitter.com/LASparksPR/status/1665900599324602368?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 6, 2023</a>The Sparks have established a new identity under Curt Miller, while the Sky have doubled down on theirs under James Wade. Both like to play with pace, and have their own quirks that make them interesting.The Sparks are the league’s best at forcing turnovers. The Sky commit the second-most turnovers. Both teams are top three in three-point shooting and top four in assists. This could turn into a high-scoring affair.Phoenix Mercury @ Indiana Fever, June 11, 5 p.m. ESTWhere to watch: CBS Sports, Facebook, IndianaFever, AZ Family 3TV, AZ Family Sports Network 44Five words describe the intrigue in this one: Aliyah Boston versus Brittney Griner. This season’s No. 1 pick will face off against one of the best to ever do it in what will be her (literal) biggest matchup so far.This is also a matchup of two teams in similar spots in the rankings, but vastly different paths there. The Mercury are a veteran team that have been showing their age in a bad way. They have some bad losses against teams they were expected to be better than. Meanwhile, the Fever are a young team showing theirs in the best ways possible. They have played some great, competitive games against some of the league’s best teams.The stylistic matchup is interesting, too. The Fever are the league’s third-best rebounding team, while the Mercury are last. The Mercury also average the most turnovers in the league by a sizable margin, averaging 6.5 more than the Fever do. Still, the Mercury shoot 46 percent from the field, second best in the league, to the Fever’s 40.4, which is tenth. The teams are the top two fouling teams in the league, though, which could be a big factor in this one. <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/wnba-power-rankings-3-best-games-week-3/">WNBA Week Three: 3 must-see matchups this week</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://us.yorba.org/wnba-power-rankings-3-best-games-week-3/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
