<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>America Archives - Yorba Foundation</title>
	<atom:link href="http://us.yorba.org/tag/america/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://us.yorba.org/tag/america/</link>
	<description>USA</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:48:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>&#039;Stamped From The Beginning&#039;: History of Racism in America Gets Graphic Novel Adaptation</title>
		<link>http://us.yorba.org/stamped-from-beginning-graphic-novel-racism-american-history/</link>
					<comments>http://us.yorba.org/stamped-from-beginning-graphic-novel-racism-american-history/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[usyorba]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:48:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Movie]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[039Stamped]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adaptation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[America]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Beginning039]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Graphic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Racism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://us.yorba.org/?p=74</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A vitally important and visually stunning new graphic novel, Stamped from the Beginning: The Definitive History of Racist Ideas in America, adapts MacArthur Genius Grant winner Dr. Ibram X. Kendi&#8217;s 2016 book...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/stamped-from-beginning-graphic-novel-racism-american-history/">&#039;Stamped From The Beginning&#039;: History of Racism in America Gets Graphic Novel Adaptation</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img decoding="async" src="https://static1.srcdn.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/stamped-from-the-beginning.jpg" /><br />
A vitally important and visually stunning new graphic novel, Stamped from the Beginning: The Definitive History of Racist Ideas in America, adapts MacArthur Genius Grant winner Dr. Ibram X. Kendi&#8217;s 2016 book of the same name. This new medium makes Kendi&#8217;s acclaimed history book more accessible and digestible to a variety of readers.</p>
<p>Kendi is a National Book Award-winning historian and the founder and director of Boston University&#8217;s Center for Antiracist Research. He worked closely with award-winning cartoonist and historian Joel Christian Gill to adapt Stamped from the Beginning into the graphic novel format. Their collaboration gives the critically necessary text new life in 2023 amidst continued violence against Black and Brown bodies across the United States.<br />
SCREENRANT VIDEO OF THE DAYSCROLL TO CONTINUE WITH CONTENT</p>
<p>Stamped from the Beginning: The Definitive History of Racist Ideas in America is an impressive and disturbing weaving of the United States&#8217; horrifically racist roots, the institutional and interpersonal racism still pervasive in American society today, and the ways in which antiracist movements can inspire hope and change. These important lessons are all wrapped up in truly gorgeous and evocative art by Joel Christian Gill for the new graphic novel format.</p>
<p>Racism has persisted throughout history—but so have antiracist efforts to dismantle it. Through deep research and a gripping narrative that illuminates the lives of five key American figures, preeminent historian Ibram X. Kendi reveals how understanding and improving the world cannot happen without identifying and facing the racist forces that shape it.</p>
<p>Related: <a href="https://screenrant.com/run-john-lewis-march-graphic-novel-civil-rights/">Rep. John Lewis&#8217; RUN Tells the Untold Story of the Civil Rights Movement</a></p>
<p> Confronting America&#8217;s Racist Past, Present, and Potential Future </p>
<p>Kendi argues that &#8220;&#8230;the root of these tragedies&#8230; is a lineage of racist ideas that have endured and continue to be reproduced throughout the history and present of the United States, ideas that continually justify racist policies.&#8221; This new graphic novel was adapted beginning in 2020 amidst protests caused by the murders of Breonna Taylor, Ahmaud Arbery, Jacob Blake <a href="https://screenrant.com/do-right-thing-george-floyd-protest-video-spike-lee/">and George Floyd</a>. It aims to make complex ideas about race and racism, and the history of how racism has shaped and continues to guide the United States, very digestible to a variety of readers who may have little exposure to this topic. This adaptation is incredibly important because the more people who gain access to the critically important writings of Kendi, the more the public can understand the impact of conservative politicians&#8217; battles against things like <a href="https://screenrant.com/keeping-up-kardashians-caitlyn-jenner-race-schools-politics/">Critical Race Theory being taught in schools</a>.</p>
<p>Stamped from the Beginning shows that unfiltered history, truth, accountability, and pursuit of justice are the critical components of building an antiracist culture and future, ideals that are being destroyed by recent movements towards book banning and resegregation. The new graphic novel adaptation is a vast and decades spanning history of how racist ideas first rooted in America. It is grounded in the exploration of five key American figures who have impacted the development and change of the United States since its founding: Cotton Mather, Thomas Jefferson, William Lloyd Garrison, W.E.B. Du Bois, and Angela Davis. Stamped from the Beginning made a major splash in the world of politics, education, and antiracist activism when it first debuted in 2016. Now the &#8220;culture defining&#8221; text is even more necessary than ever, making the graphic novel adaptation&#8217;s accessibility to younger readers and those unfamiliar with its concepts and histories even more critical.</p>
<p>Kendi&#8217;s book was a critical and imperative text when it first debuted in 2016. This stunning new graphic novel adaptation of Stamped from the Beginning: The Definitive History of Racist Ideas in America comes at a time when racial justice and antiracist activism is facing more pushback than has been seen in years, making its approachability and illustrated breakdowns of racist ideas and their impact more important than ever.</p>
<p>Stamped from the Beginning: The Definitive History of Racist Ideas in America is available now.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/stamped-from-beginning-graphic-novel-racism-american-history/">&#039;Stamped From The Beginning&#039;: History of Racism in America Gets Graphic Novel Adaptation</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://us.yorba.org/stamped-from-beginning-graphic-novel-racism-american-history/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
