<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Lions Archives - Yorba Foundation</title>
	<atom:link href="http://us.yorba.org/tag/lions/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://us.yorba.org/tag/lions/</link>
	<description>USA</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:54:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Lions: Dan Campbell thinks Jared Goff has improved without Sean McVay</title>
		<link>http://us.yorba.org/lions-dan-campbell-jared-goff-improvement-sean-mcvay/</link>
					<comments>http://us.yorba.org/lions-dan-campbell-jared-goff-improvement-sean-mcvay/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[usyorba]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:54:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Campbell]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Goff]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[improved]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jared]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[McVay]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sean]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[thinks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://us.yorba.org/?p=95</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Dan Campbell believes Jared Goff is a better quarterback for him than he was playing for Sean McVay’s Los Angeles Rams.Look at Dan Campbell driving the Jared Goff hype train, man!Together, the...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/lions-dan-campbell-jared-goff-improvement-sean-mcvay/">Lions: Dan Campbell thinks Jared Goff has improved without Sean McVay</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p> Dan Campbell believes Jared Goff is a better quarterback for him than he was playing for Sean McVay’s Los Angeles Rams.Look at Dan Campbell driving the Jared Goff hype train, man!Together, the <a href="http://fansided.com/nfl/teams/detroit-lions">Detroit Lions</a> are well on their way towards building something special. After narrowly missing out on the NFC playoffs a year ago, one could argue that Detroit is the favorite to come out of the NFC North this season. A big reason for that has been the play of Goff. Campbell went as far to say Goff is a better quarterback now than with the Sean McVay <a href="http://fansided.com/nfl/teams/los-angeles-rams">Los Angeles Rams</a>.While I’m sure a lot of it has to do working with offensive coordinator Ben Johnson and quarterbacks coach Mark Brunell, it’s not like Goff was a scrub coming out of Cal. He played for Sonny Dykes and was the No. 1 overall pick by the Rams in the 2016 <a href="http://fansided.com/nfl/nfl-draft">NFL Draft</a> for a reason!Here is what Campbell had to say at the podium on Tuesday when speaking with the media.“His confidence has really grown … he’s a better quarterback than he was [in L.A.], in my opinion… we’ve come lightyears ahead of where he was two years ago when we started teaching him protections.”This is the entire clip of Campbell speaking with the Lions media about Goff and other big topics.The best part is the Lions are finally pulling in the same direction. It had been a while, to be honest.Dan Campbell feels Jared Goff is a better quarterback now with the Detroit LionsLook. I love everything about this comment from Campbell. It is fantastic. Goff always had talent. I remember watching him sling the pill around for Cal when the Golden Bears weren’t the least bit good and I thought to myself, “Oh, there is something here for sure!” Unfortunately, he played for the worst offenses of my lifetime on the 2016 Rams for Jeff Fisher. That would’ve ruined anyone.After not knowing where the sun went, Goff emerged as a Pro Bowl-caliber passer for the Rams for the next four years. Sadly, it wasn’t good enough for McVay, so he convinced owner Stan Kroenke to trade for fellow Georgia boy Matthew Stafford. Together, McVay and Stafford won a <a href="http://fansided.com/nfl/super-bowl">Super Bowl</a>. While the Lions stunk two years ago, they have the better ceiling … because of Goff.Yes, Detroit may have drafted Hendon Hooker out of Tennessee, but I am nowhere near as high on him as I was Goff coming out of Cal. He may be the future of Lions football, or he may just be a backup. Regardless, look for Goff to continue to grow in Johnson’s offense for as long as he remains in Detroit, as well as build on his rapport with Johnson’s potential successor in Brunell.See, Goff throws a beautiful spiral, but does need a savvy offensive mind to set him up for success to make plays down the field. In time, Goff will grow and mature into his late 20s, now that the cerebral part of his game has caught up to his natural gifts as a passer. Either way, I don’t think we’ve seen the best football out of Goff yet. He is why I am so excited about this Lions this season.If Goff plays up to his standard, Detroit could become one of the eight best teams in all of football. </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/lions-dan-campbell-jared-goff-improvement-sean-mcvay/">Lions: Dan Campbell thinks Jared Goff has improved without Sean McVay</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://us.yorba.org/lions-dan-campbell-jared-goff-improvement-sean-mcvay/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
