<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Uncategorised Archives - Yorba Foundation</title>
	<atom:link href="http://us.yorba.org/category/uncategorised/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://us.yorba.org/category/uncategorised/</link>
	<description>USA</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 20:27:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>In shocking twist, PGA Tour and LIV Golf to merge</title>
		<link>http://us.yorba.org/in-shocking-twist-pga-tour-and-liv-golf-to-merge/</link>
					<comments>http://us.yorba.org/in-shocking-twist-pga-tour-and-liv-golf-to-merge/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[usyorba]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 20:27:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorised]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://us.yorba.org/?p=6</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The PGA Tour will merge with LIV Golf, ending a years-long rivalry between the two world golfing superpowers.  After years of controversy, the PGA Tour and LIV Golf are expected to engage...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/in-shocking-twist-pga-tour-and-liv-golf-to-merge/">In shocking twist, PGA Tour and LIV Golf to merge</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong><em>The PGA Tour will merge with LIV Golf, ending a years-long rivalry between the two world golfing superpowers. </em></strong></p>
<p class="speakable-content">After years of controversy, the PGA Tour and LIV Golf are expected to engage in a company merger to create a “global entity” of golfing.</p>
<p>The inaugural season for LIV Golf League, which is financially backed by the Saudi Arabia Public Investment Fund, officially started in October 2022. Several high-profile golfers joined the circuit, including recent PGA Tour winner Brooks Kopeka and golfing legend Phil Mickelson.</p>
<p>LIV’s emergence caused quite a stir in the golfing world, with the PGA essentially shunning golfers who joined the new league and engaging in a long legal battle that will now come to a peaceful conclusion.</p>
<p class="speakable-content">LIV Golf and the PGA Tour will merge, ending feud</p>
<p>“After two years of disruption and distraction, this is a historic day for the game we all know and love,” said PGA Tour commissioner Jay Monahan.</p>
<p>Previously, the two sides were engaged in bitter litigation over contract disputes, which will now be put to rest in favor of unity and financial gain. The two sides will form a “new, yet-to-be-named for-profit company” that will also include the DP World Tour (or, European PGA Tour).</p>
<p>Per CNBC’s David Faber, the Saudi P.I.F. is “prepared to invest billions [of dollars] of new capital into the new entity.” The merger will also create a “a fair and objective process” for previously renounced players to re-apply for PGA membership, according to the official press release.</p>
<p>The conflict between the PGA and LIV has been palpable. This resolution will reunite great golfers on the course while presumably leading to more investment in the game of golf and its presentation around the world. Many will say it was inevitable given the volume of noteworthy names who left the PGA Tour. In a way, this is a merger of tradition and innovation, the old and the new. It will be interesting to see the progression of professional golf in the years to come.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/in-shocking-twist-pga-tour-and-liv-golf-to-merge/">In shocking twist, PGA Tour and LIV Golf to merge</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://us.yorba.org/in-shocking-twist-pga-tour-and-liv-golf-to-merge/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
