<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Brian Archives - Yorba Foundation</title>
	<atom:link href="http://us.yorba.org/tag/brian/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://us.yorba.org/tag/brian/</link>
	<description>USA</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:23:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Brian Snitker wisely reinserts Marcell Ozuna into lineup after benching</title>
		<link>http://us.yorba.org/brian-snitker-marcell-ozuna-reinserted-braves-lineup/</link>
					<comments>http://us.yorba.org/brian-snitker-marcell-ozuna-reinserted-braves-lineup/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[usyorba]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:23:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[benching]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brian]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[lineup]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marcell]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ozuna]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[reinserts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Snitker]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[wisely]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://us.yorba.org/?p=56</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Atlanta Braves manager Brian Snitker made the right call by reinserting Marcell Ozuna into the starting lineup after his benching on Sunday.It took two days, but Marcell Ozuna will be back in...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/brian-snitker-marcell-ozuna-reinserted-braves-lineup/">Brian Snitker wisely reinserts Marcell Ozuna into lineup after benching</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p> Atlanta Braves manager Brian Snitker made the right call by reinserting Marcell Ozuna into the starting lineup after his benching on Sunday.It took two days, but Marcell Ozuna will be back in the starting lineup for the <a href="http://fansided.com/mlb/mlb-teams/atlanta-braves">Atlanta Braves</a> vs. the <a href="http://fansided.com/mlb/mlb-teams/new-york-mets">New York Mets</a> after getting benched in Sunday’s series finale vs. the <a href="http://fansided.com/mlb/mlb-teams/arizona-diamondbacks">Arizona Diamondbacks</a>.Braves skipper Brian Snitker pulled the controversial designated hitter from the game in favor of backstop Sean Murphy. This had everything to do with Ozuna not hustling out of the box on what was a 415-foot single to deep centerfield. Ozuna thought he parked one, but because he wasn’t running hard, he was unable to get extra bases on a critical play in a crucial game vs. an NL foe.After an off-day, Snitker did the right thing by penciling Ozuna into the starting lineup on Tuesday.Ozuna will bat seventh as the Atlanta DH in Game 1 of their home series vs. the arch rival Mets.Atlanta Braves: Brian Snitker made right call in starting Marcell Ozuna TuesdayLook. This has nothing to do with how Ozuna does at the plate in this game, or in this series, for that matter. It’s about a manager and one of his players being on the same page in doing whatever is necessary to win games. Snitker had to pull Ozuna from the game, and Ozuna knew it. Bobby Cox did this to Andruw Jones back in the day. It doesn’t happen often, but these things do happen.We’re talking about professionals who play and manage a children’s game for a living. Nothing is given here, it is earned. Surely, Ozuna feels terrible about not playing up to his standard in that moment in Phoenix. However, I think it’s great that they can move forward in this and try to win anyway. The best part is Ozuna has hit very well at the plate for the better part of five weeks now.Overall, you had to have been out of your gourd to think Snitker was going to permanently bench Ozuna for marveling at his long single. You probably got chastised at some point playing youth baseball or softball on a similar play. We are all human! Above all else, why would Snitker keep one of <a href="http://fansided.com/mlb">MLB</a>‘s most dangerous right-handed hitters on the bench when his OPS of late is 1.000-plus?The Mets are in town, so nothing else matters. Focus all of your attention to beat the hated Mets! </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/brian-snitker-marcell-ozuna-reinserted-braves-lineup/">Brian Snitker wisely reinserts Marcell Ozuna into lineup after benching</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://us.yorba.org/brian-snitker-marcell-ozuna-reinserted-braves-lineup/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
