<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Senior Archives - Yorba Foundation</title>
	<atom:link href="http://us.yorba.org/tag/senior/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://us.yorba.org/tag/senior/</link>
	<description>USA</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:26:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>The Importance of Regular Vet Check-Ups for Senior Cats with Joint Issues</title>
		<link>http://us.yorba.org/regular-vet-check-ups/</link>
					<comments>http://us.yorba.org/regular-vet-check-ups/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[usyorba]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:26:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cats]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CheckUps]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Importance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Joint]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regular]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Senior]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vet]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://us.yorba.org/?p=59</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As cat owners, our shared goal is to provide our kitty companions with the best quality of life; regular vet check-ups. However, as they age, joint problems can become more frequent, negatively impacting...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/regular-vet-check-ups/">The Importance of Regular Vet Check-Ups for Senior Cats with Joint Issues</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p>
<p>As cat owners, our shared goal is to provide our kitty companions with the best quality of life; regular vet check-ups. However, as they age, joint problems can become more frequent, negatively impacting their quality of life and mobility.</p>
<p>In this short piece, we will look at the importance of senior cats getting regular vet checkups, especially if they have joint problems, and how such checkups may help keep your furry companions healthy and active for many years to come.</p>
<p>Optimizing Quality of Life</p>
<p>Your feline buddies will likely start experiencing joint discomfort and other movement problems as they age. Even though this is a typical problem in older cats, you must monitor your cat’s health and regularly take them in for checkups at the veterinarian.As senior cats begin to experience arthritis and other age-related disorders, joint pain is a problem that frequently arises for these animals. Even though there is no known cure for these medical conditions, there are treatments available that can help you keep your cat comfortable and manage their pain. </p>
<p>Checkups at the veterinarian on a routine basis are essential for elderly cats who have joint difficulties since they can assist in the early detection of any unusual behaviours and ensure that your cat is receiving the best possible care. </p>
<p>Most vet services, like the <a href="https://thevets.com/our-locations/texas/dallas/fort-worth/">mobile vet service in Fort Worth, TX,</a> will most likely suggest modifying your cat’s food or exercise routine and prescribing medications or nutritional supplements to ease their discomfort. </p>
<p>It’s essential to take this advice and follow suggestions from the professionals to help you take good care of your pet friends. It’s important to stress that any time you suspect your cat may be suffering from joint pains, do not hesitate to consult with your senior cat’s veterinarian. </p>
<p>See also: <a href="https://kiiky.com/wealth/ways-to-make-money-from-dogs/">10 Best Ways To Make Money From Dogs In 2023</a></p>
<p>What are the Signs of Joint Pain and Arthritis in Senior Cats?</p>
<p>It’s not unusual for your<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Aging_in_cats" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"> aging cats</a> to begin displaying symptoms of joint pain and arthritis. This is a regular aspect of getting older, but it can be made worse by being overweight, having an injury, or having a medical condition. There are several symptoms of arthritis and joint discomfort in cats, and we discuss some below:1. One symptom is a decrease in your cat’s activity level and an increase in immobility. When they walk or try to get up from a lying posture, they may appear stiff.<br />2. In addition to mobility issues, you may find that your cat may seem not to show interest in most things in its surroundings. They could be sleeping longer and being less active than usual.<br />3. Your cat may be in pain if they show discomfort when you touch them near their joints or howl when you lift them up. They may be showing discomfort if you find that touching the area around their neck, back, or legs causes them distress. Limping or an unusual gait may be an indication of joint pain.<br />4. A loss in appetite is a common side effect of joint discomfort because it makes eating and moving about more challenging. Cats suffering from joint pain can experience weight loss due to their decreased appetite.<br />5. they may exhibit changes in grooming behavior. Cats with joint pain may have trouble grooming themselves, which can lead to changes in the cat’s appearance and smell.</p>
<p>How Can Regular Vet Check-Ups Help?</p>
<p>While arthritis cannot be cured, it can be treated, and your cat can be helped to maintain an easier life. Having your pet examined by a veterinarian regularly is a significant first step. Your vet can prescribe pain medication and suggest nutritional supplements and dietary adjustments. </p>
<p>Arthritic cats can be treated with various options, including medication, vitamins, physical therapy, weight management, and even acupuncture. Your senior cat can enjoy a long and happy life with your gentle care. </p>
<p>Visiting the vet regularly will also help detect other problems, such as kidney disease or diabetes, in their early stages. So, to keeping your senior cat healthy and happy requires routine visits to the vet.</p>
<p>Read also: <a href="https://kiiky.com/wealth/healthy-paws-pet-insurance/">Healthy Paws Pet Insurance Reviews 2022</a></p>
<p>Tips to Keep Senior Cats Moving Despite Joint Issues</p>
<p>1. Keep them at a healthy weight – excess weight puts added strain on already weak joints.</p>
<p>2. Encourage movement – create an environment that encourages your cat to move around, such as placing their food and water in different areas of the house.</p>
<p>3. Avoid slippery surfaces – provide traction for your cat by placing rugs or mats around the house strategically.</p>
<p>4. Invest in joint supplements – ask your veterinarian about supplements that can help reduce inflammation and pain in your cat’s joints.</p>
<p><a href="https://kiiky.com/wealth/regular-vet-check-ups/Is It Legit Or Scam?">Read: Figo Pet Insurance Reviews 2023: Is It Legit Or Scam?</a></p>
<p>Other Recommendations to Consider for Senior Cats with Joint Issues</p>
<p>There is a wide selection of veterinary care that is indicated for senior cats who are experiencing joint problems. Veterinarians may suggest programs to help your cat lose weight or get more exercise, as well as specific foods, supplements, or drugs. They could also recommend joint injections or surgery when the condition is more severe.</p>
<p>The following are some general things to keep in mind when caring for an older cat who has joint problems:</p>
<p>Ensuring that they have access to a relaxing environment where they can sleep and rest.</p>
<p> Ensuring that food and water dishes are conveniently located for them to use.</p>
<p> Keeping their fingernails and toenails clipped.</p>
<p>Avoid short play and anything else that could cause more discomfort or injury.</p>
<p>Conclusion</p>
<p>Checkups at the vet on a regular schedule are essential for elderly cats that have joint problems. These checkups can help detect any changes in the cat’s health and alert you to potential sources of discomfort. It is essential to maintain your cat’s health as they age by ensuring that their vaccines are up-to-date, giving them nourishment that is appropriate for their age, and helping them to maintain their mobility. </p>
<p>You can make sure your senior cat is able to live a happy and comfortable life despite the joint problems they may have by making preparations and devoting better attention to its care.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/regular-vet-check-ups/">The Importance of Regular Vet Check-Ups for Senior Cats with Joint Issues</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://us.yorba.org/regular-vet-check-ups/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
