<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>list Archives - Yorba Foundation</title>
	<atom:link href="http://us.yorba.org/tag/list/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://us.yorba.org/tag/list/</link>
	<description>USA</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:56:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Conn Smythe odds: Jonathan Marchessault tops list to win playoff MVP</title>
		<link>http://us.yorba.org/conn-smythe-odds-jonathan-marchessault-tops-list-win-playoff-mvp/</link>
					<comments>http://us.yorba.org/conn-smythe-odds-jonathan-marchessault-tops-list-win-playoff-mvp/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[usyorba]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:56:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conn]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jonathan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[list]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marchessault]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MVP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[odds]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[playoff]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Smythe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tops]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[win]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://us.yorba.org/?p=104</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>May 12, 2023; Las Vegas, Nevada, USA; Vegas Golden Knights right wing Jonathan Marchessault (81) warms up before the start of game five of the second round of the 2023 Stanley Cup...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/conn-smythe-odds-jonathan-marchessault-tops-list-win-playoff-mvp/">Conn Smythe odds: Jonathan Marchessault tops list to win playoff MVP</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://images2.minutemediacdn.com/image/fetch/w_850,h_560,c_fill,g_auto,f_auto/https%3A%2F%2Ffansided.com%2Fwp-content%2Fuploads%2Fimagn-images%2F2023%2F06%2F20654564-850x560.jpeg" rel="attachment wp-att-2425421"/>May 12, 2023; Las Vegas, Nevada, USA; Vegas Golden Knights right wing Jonathan Marchessault (81) warms up before the start of game five of the second round of the 2023 Stanley Cup Playoffs against the Edmonton Oilers at T-Mobile Arena. Mandatory Credit: Stephen R. Sylvanie-USA TODAY Sports<a href="https://fansided.com/2023/06/06/aaron-judge-toe-injury-yankees/" rel="prev">Aaron Judge injury update: Things don’t look good for Yankees by Kristen Wong</a><a href="https://fansided.com/2023/06/06/lions-dan-campbell-jared-goff-improvement-sean-mcvay/" rel="next">Lions: Dan Campbell thinks Jared Goff has improved without Sean McVay by John Buhler</a>     The Vegas Golden Knights have taken over as a <a href="https://fansided.com/2023/06/06/golden-knights-stanley-cup-odds-skyrocket-game-2-win/" rel="">sizable favorite to win the Stanley Cup</a> after taking a 2-0 series lead over the Florida Panthers.As a result, the Conn Smythe Trophy odds have also shifted. The award is given to the MVP of the NHL Playoffs and it’s almost always given to a player belonging to the winning team. So, as you’d expect, players on the Golden Knights are starting to float to the top of the odds list.Let’s take a look at the latest odds to win the Conn Smythe heading into Game 3 in Florida.Conn Smythe Trophy oddsConn Smythe Trophy &#8211; 2022-23Odds updated June 6th, 2023, at 4:46 pmJonathan Marchessault is the new betting favorite to win the Conn Smythe Trophy at -105 odds, which is an implied probability of 51.22%.Marchessault has been hot in the playoffs dating back to the last round. He now has 21 points in 19 postseason games, including a three goals and an assist in the first two games against the Panthers.<a href="https://bit.ly/FanSided-Web-DraftKings" class="chakra-linkbox__overlay css-1cst4gr" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">DraftKings</a>New Users: Bet $5 on Any NHL Playoff Game, Get $200 in Bonus Bets Instantly!<a target="_blank" rel="noopener" class="chakra-link css-1hhai3c" href="https://bit.ly/FanSided-Web-DraftKings">New customers only. 21+ (18+ WY) and present in AZ, CO, CT, IL, IN, IA, KS, LA, MD, MI, NJ, NY, PA, TN, VA, WV, WY. All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements. See full terms at sportsbook.draftkings.com/footballterms. Valid 1 per new customer. Minimum $5 deposit and wager required. Rewards issued as non-withdrawable free bets or site credits (i.e. if your wager wins you receive a $200 bonus paid as 8 free bets of $25 each in addition to any cash winnings from original wager). Gambling Problem? Call/text 1-800-GAMBLER (IL/NJ/PA/WV), call/text 1-800-522-4700 (CO/KS/LA/WY), call 1-800-NEXT-STEP or text NEXTSTEP to 53342 (AZ), call 888-789-7777 or visit ccpg.org/chat (CT), call 1-800-BETS-OFF or visit yourlifeiowa.org/gambling (IA), call 1-800-9-WITH-IT or text INGAMB to 53342 (IN), call 1-800-270-7117 (MI), call (877-8-HOPENY) or text HOPENY (467369) (NY), call/text TN REDLINE 1-800-889-9789 (TN) or call/text 1-888-532-3500 (VA).</a>Read moreJack Eichel is second on the odds list, recording 22 points in the 19 games. With that being said, he only six of his points are goals. With goals held at a higher regard than assists, Marchessault has the edge with his 12 goals.The interesting dark horse is Adin Hill, the goaltender for the Golden Knights, at +500. He has quietly been phenomenal in the playoffs, sporting a 2.06 goals against average and a .937 save percentage in 13 games and 11 starts in the playoffs.The favorite at the start of the Stanley Cup Final, Sergei Bobrovsky, has fallen all the way to +1300 after two poor performances in the first two games. He was even pulled from the net in Game 2 after allowing four goals on just 13 shots.If the Golden Knights win Game 3, all Panthers on the odds list are going to continue to fall down the odds board.<a href="https://bit.ly/FanSided-Web-Caesars" class="chakra-linkbox__overlay css-1cst4gr" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Caesars</a>Get Your First Bet on Caesars up to $1,250 When You Bet Any NHL Game!<a target="_blank" rel="noopener" class="chakra-link css-1hhai3c" href="https://bit.ly/FanSided-Web-Caesars">21+ only. Offer valid and must be physically present in AZ, CO, IL, IN, IA, KS, LA, MI, NJ, NY, PA, TN, VA, WV &amp; WY only. New users and first $10+ wager only. Must register with eligible promo code. Bet amount of qualifying wager returned only if wager is settled as a loss. Maximum bet credit $1,250; must be used within 14 days of receipt. Tier Credits and Reward Credits will be added to account within 7 days after qualifying wager settles. Void where prohibited. Know When To Stop Before You Start® Gambling Problem? AZ: Call 1-800-NEXT-STEP; CO, WY, KS (Affiliated with Kansas Crossing Casino): Call 1-800-522-4700; IN: Call 1-800-9-WITH-IT; IA: Call 1-800-BETSOFF; LA: Call 1-877-770-STOP (licensed through Horseshoe Bossier City and Harrah’s New Orleans); MI: Call 1-800-270-7117; IL, NJ, VA, WV, PA (Affiliated with Harrah&#8217;s Philadelphia): If you or someone you know has a gambling problem, crisis counseling and referral services can be accessed by calling 1-800-GAMBLER (1-800-426-2537) or WV: visit 1800gambler.net. TN: Call or text TN REDLINE at 1-800-889-9789. ©2022, Caesars Entertainment. Gambling problem? Call 877-8-HOPENY or text HOPENY (467369). See Caesars.com/promos for full terms. Read More</a>Read more<a href="https://bit.ly/FanSided-Web-FanDuel" class="chakra-linkbox__overlay css-1cst4gr" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">FanDuel</a>Limited Time: Get a No Sweat First Bet up to $2,500 on the NHL Finals!<a target="_blank" rel="noopener" class="chakra-link css-1hhai3c" href="https://bit.ly/FanSided-Web-FanDuel">$10 first deposit required. Up to $2,500 back in free bets if you lose first online real money wager. New customers only. 21+ and present in AZ, CO, CT, IA, IL, IN, LA (permitted parishes only), MD, MI, NJ, NY, PA, TN, VA, WY, or WV. Restrictions apply. See full terms at sportsbook.fanduel.com. Gambling Problem? Call 1-800-GAMBLER (IL/MD/NJ/PA/WV) or visit mdgamblinghelp.org (MD), 1-800-522-4700 (CO/KS/WY), 1-800-NEXT-STEP or text NEXTSTEP to 53342 (AZ), 1-888-789-7777 or visit ccpg.org/chat (CT), 1-800-BETS-OFF (IA), 1-800-9-WITH-IT or text INGAMB to 53342 (IN), 1-877-770-STOP (LA), 1-800-270-7117 (MI), 1-877-8-HOPENY or text HOPENY (467369) (NY), TN REDLINE 1-800-889-9789 (TN), and 1-888-532-3500 (VA).</a>Read more–Game odds refresh periodically and are subject to change.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/conn-smythe-odds-jonathan-marchessault-tops-list-win-playoff-mvp/">Conn Smythe odds: Jonathan Marchessault tops list to win playoff MVP</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://us.yorba.org/conn-smythe-odds-jonathan-marchessault-tops-list-win-playoff-mvp/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
