<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>usyorba, Author at Yorba Foundation</title>
	<atom:link href="http://us.yorba.org/author/usyorba/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://us.yorba.org/author/usyorba/</link>
	<description>USA</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 22:00:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>How to Become a Taylormade Product Tester in 2023 &#124; Full Guide</title>
		<link>http://us.yorba.org/how-to-become-a-taylormade-product-tester-in-2023-full-guide/</link>
					<comments>http://us.yorba.org/how-to-become-a-taylormade-product-tester-in-2023-full-guide/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[usyorba]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 22:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Full]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guide]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Product]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Taylormade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tester]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://us.yorba.org/?p=107</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Are you a golf enthusiast looking for an opportunity to test and provide feedback on the latest and greatest golf equipment from Taylormade? Well, look no further! In this guide, we will...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/how-to-become-a-taylormade-product-tester-in-2023-full-guide/">How to Become a Taylormade Product Tester in 2023 | Full Guide</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p>
<p>Are you a golf enthusiast looking for an opportunity to test and provide feedback on the latest and greatest golf equipment from Taylormade? Well, look no further! In this guide, we will provide you with all the information you need to become a Taylormade product tester in 2023.</p>
<p>As a Taylormade product tester, you will have the opportunity to get your hands on the latest golf equipment before it hits the market. You’ll be able to provide valuable feedback to Taylormade’s research and development team, helping them to create even better golf clubs, balls, and accessories.</p>
<p>But how do you become a Taylormade product tester? It’s quite simple. First, you’ll need to fill out an application on Taylormade’s website. Then, if you meet their criteria, you’ll be added to their product testing pool. From there, you’ll be selected to test products based on your profile and the specific needs of Taylormade’s research team.</p>
<p>In this guide, we’ll walk you through the entire process of becoming a Taylormade product tester. We’ll provide you with tips on how to fill out your application, what to expect during the testing process, and how to provide the best feedback possible. So, grab your golf clubs, and let’s get started!</p>
<p>Who is a Taylormade Product Tester?</p>
<p>A Taylormade product tester is a golf enthusiast who is selected to test and provide feedback on the latest golf equipment from Taylormade. These individuals are avid golfers who have a deep passion for the game and a desire to help improve the golf equipment industry.</p>
<p>Taylormade product testers play a crucial role in the development of new golf equipment. They provide valuable feedback on everything from the performance and feel of golf clubs to the durability and design of golf balls and accessories. Their insights and opinions help Taylormade’s research and development team to make informed decisions about how to improve their products.</p>
<p>Product testers are selected based on their golfing experience, playing ability, and other factors that may be relevant to the specific product being tested. Taylormade typically looks for testers who are dedicated and committed to providing detailed feedback throughout the testing process.</p>
<p>Being a Taylormade product tester is a unique opportunity to get hands-on experience with the latest and greatest golf equipment. It allows golf enthusiasts to play an active role in shaping the future of the golf industry and to have a direct impact on the products that millions of golfers use around the world.</p>
<p>Why Does Taylormade Hire Product Testers?</p>
<p>Taylormade hires product testers for a variety of reasons. First and foremost, they want to ensure that their products are of the highest quality and meet the needs of golfers at all skill levels. By getting feedback from a diverse group of product testers, Taylormade can gain valuable insights into how their products perform and how they can be improved.</p>
<p>Product testers also play a key role in the development process. By providing feedback on prototypes and early versions of products, they help Taylormade’s research and development team to identify any issues or areas for improvement before the products are released to the general public. This can save Taylormade time and money in the long run and help them to create better products overall.</p>
<p>In addition, hiring product testers allows Taylormade to build stronger relationships with its customers. By involving golf enthusiasts in the development process, Taylormade can show that they value and respect the opinions of their customers. This can help to build brand loyalty and create a community of dedicated Taylormade users.</p>
<p>Taylormade hires product testers to improve the quality of their products, gain valuable insights into their performance, and build stronger relationships with their customers.</p>
<p>Read: <a target="_blank" href="https://kiiky.com/wealth/american-consumer-panels/" rel="noreferrer noopener">American Consumer Panels 2023: A New Product Testing Scam?</a></p>
<p>Is Taylormade Product Tester Legit?</p>
<p>Yes, Taylormade product testing is a legitimate program offered by the company. Taylormade is a well-respected and established golf equipment manufacturer that has been in business for decades. Their product testing program is designed to gather feedback from golf enthusiasts and improve the quality of their products.</p>
<p>Taylormade’s product testing program is transparent and open to anyone who meets their criteria. They have a thorough application process and select testers based on their golfing experience, playing ability, and other factors that may be relevant to the specific product being tested. They also provide testers with detailed instructions on how to test the products and provide feedback.</p>
<p>Taylormade’s product testing program is a legitimate and valuable opportunity for golf enthusiasts to get hands-on experience with the latest golf equipment and provide feedback to one of the top golf equipment manufacturers in the world.</p>
<p>How to Become a Taylormade Product Tester</p>
<p>ChatGPT</p>
<p>Becoming a Taylormade product tester is a straightforward process. The first step is to visit Taylormade’s website and navigate to the product testing section. There, you will be asked to fill out an application form with some basic information about yourself and your golfing experience.</p>
<p>Once you have submitted your application, Taylormade will review it and determine if you meet their criteria for product testers. If you are selected, you will be added to their product testing pool and may be contacted when they have a new product to test.</p>
<p>If you are chosen to test a product, Taylormade will typically send it to you along with detailed instructions on how to use and evaluate it. You will be asked to test the product under various conditions and provide feedback on its performance, feel, and other relevant factors.</p>
<p>Being a product tester is a serious responsibility. Taylormade relies on testers to provide accurate and detailed feedback that can help them improve their products. As such, you must take the testing process seriously and provide thoughtful and honest feedback.</p>
<p>What are the Eligibility Requirements for Taylormade Product Tester?</p>
<p>To become a Taylormade product tester, there are several eligibility requirements that you must meet. These requirements may vary depending on the specific product being tested, but in general, they include the following:</p>
<p>Age: Testers must be at least 18 years old.</p>
<p> Golfing experience: Testers should have a strong knowledge of and passion for golf. They should be able to provide detailed feedback on the performance of golf equipment.</p>
<p> Playing ability: Testers should have a decent level of playing ability, as they will be testing products under various playing conditions. While a low handicap is not necessarily required, testers should be able to provide feedback that is relevant and helpful.</p>
<p> Location: Testers should be located in the United States, as this is where Taylormade’s product testing program is based.</p>
<p> Availability: Testers should be able to commit to testing the product thoroughly and providing detailed feedback within the designated time frame.</p>
<p>Note that meeting these eligibility requirements does not guarantee that you will be selected as a product tester. Taylormade receives a large number of applications and selects testers based on a variety of factors, including their golfing experience and demographic information. However, by meeting these eligibility requirements and submitting a thoughtful and detailed application, you can increase your chances of being selected as a Taylormade product tester.</p>
<p>See Also: <a target="_blank" href="https://kiiky.com/wealth/free-bulk-product-samples/" rel="noreferrer noopener">15 Ways To Get Free Bulk Product Samples From A Manufacturer In 2023</a></p>
<p>Do Taylormade Product Testers Get Paid?</p>
<p>Taylormade product testers do not typically get paid for their participation in the testing program. Instead, they are allowed to test out new products and provide feedback on their performance, feelings, and other relevant factors.</p>
<p>However, Taylormade does offer some incentives to product testers. For example, testers may be allowed to keep the products they have tested as a thank-you for their participation. Additionally, testers may receive early access to new products before they are released to the general public.</p>
<p>While product testing may not be a paid opportunity, it can still be a valuable experience for golf enthusiasts. Testers get the chance to try out new equipment and provide feedback that can help Taylormade improve its products and better meet the needs of golfers at all skill levels.</p>
<p>Are there available Taylormade Product Tester Jobs?</p>
<p>Here are the best Taylormade Product Tester jobs:</p>
<p>Golf Ball Tester</p>
<p>As a golf ball tester, you would be responsible for thoroughly testing and evaluating the performance of TaylorMade’s golf balls. This would require hitting a large number of shots using different ball models and providing detailed feedback on their performance, including factors such as distance, spin, and feel.</p>
<p>Golf ball testers need to be knowledgeable about the game of golf, as well as ball design and materials. They must also have excellent communication skills to effectively convey their feedback to the product development team.</p>
<p>Irons Tester</p>
<p>An irons tester is responsible for testing and evaluating the performance of TaylorMade’s iron sets. This involves hitting a large number of shots with different iron models and providing feedback on their performance, including factors such as distance, accuracy, and feel. Irons testers must have a deep understanding of the game of golf and iron design, as well as the ability to communicate their feedback clearly and concisely.</p>
<p>Driver Tester</p>
<p>A driver tester is responsible for evaluating the performance of TaylorMade’s drivers. This involves hitting a large number of drives with different driver models and providing feedback on their performance, including factors such as distance, accuracy, and feel.</p>
<p>Driver testers must have a strong understanding of the game of golf and driver design, as well as the ability to provide detailed and accurate feedback to the product development team.</p>
<p>Putter Tester</p>
<p>Putter testers are responsible for evaluating the performance of TaylorMade’s putters. This involves putting with different putter models and providing feedback on their performance, including factors such as feel, alignment, and consistency. Putter testers must have a deep understanding of the game of golf, as well as putter design and the various factors that affect putting performance.</p>
<p>Product Researcher</p>
<p>Product researchers are responsible for conducting research on TaylorMade’s products and the golf industry in general. This may involve analyzing market trends, conducting consumer surveys, and working with other teams to identify areas for improvement in TaylorMade’s products.</p>
<p>Product researchers must have strong analytical skills, as well as knowledge of the golf industry and consumer behavior. They must also have excellent communication skills to effectively communicate their findings to the product development team.</p>
<p>Can I Become Taylormade Product Tester from Home?</p>
<p>Becoming a Taylormade product tester from home is not an easy task, but it is possible. To become a Taylormade product tester, you need to have a strong social media presence and a passion for golf. Taylormade looks for people who are active on social media and can promote their products to a large audience.</p>
<p>One way to increase your chances of becoming a Taylormade product tester is by creating high-quality golf-related content on social media platforms such as Instagram, Twitter, and YouTube. You should also engage with other golfers and industry professionals to build your network and reputation.</p>
<p>It’s also important to keep an eye out for any opportunities that Taylormade may offer for product testing. Follow their social media accounts and sign up for their email newsletter to stay informed about any potential opportunities.</p>
<p>What is the Average Salary for a Taylormade Product Tester?</p>
<p>According to <a target="_blank" href="https://www.indeed.com/cmp/Taylormade-Golf/salaries/fitter" rel="noreferrer noopener">Indeed</a>, a popular job search and salary information website, the average salary for a product tester in the sporting goods industry is around $44,881-$60,000 per year in the United States. This estimate may give a rough idea of the salary range for a TaylorMade product tester, but it’s important to note that salaries can vary depending on various factors such as location, experience, and job responsibilities.</p>
<p>Product testers play a crucial role in the development and testing of new products, ensuring that they meet quality standards and customer needs. In the case of TaylorMade, product testers are likely to be golf enthusiasts with knowledge of the sport and experience using golf equipment. They may be responsible for testing new golf clubs, balls, and other accessories before they hit the market.</p>
<p>While salary is an important consideration when choosing a career path, it’s important to also consider other factors such as job satisfaction, work-life balance, and opportunities for growth and advancement.</p>
<p>Also, read: <a target="_blank" href="https://kiiky.com/wealth/boker-automatic-knives/" rel="noreferrer noopener">Boker Knives Reviews 2023: Products | Scam or Legit</a></p>
<p>Taylormade Product Tester Program</p>
<p>The TaylorMade Product Tester Program is a unique opportunity for avid golfers to help shape the future of golf equipment. As a product tester, you will be given the chance to test the latest TaylorMade products before they hit the market, providing valuable feedback to the company’s product development team.</p>
<p>To be considered for the program, you must be a passionate golfer with a wealth of experience using different types of golf equipment. You’ll also need to be comfortable providing detailed feedback and communicating effectively with the TaylorMade team.</p>
<p>Once accepted into the program, you’ll receive access to the latest TaylorMade products and be asked to test them under various conditions, such as on the course or at the driving range.</p>
<p>You’ll be asked to provide feedback on the product’s performance, design, and overall feel, helping to ensure that TaylorMade continues to produce high-quality golf equipment that meets the needs of golfers of all skill levels.</p>
<p>In addition to the opportunity to test new products and provide feedback, product testers may also receive other perks such as access to exclusive TaylorMade events and merchandise.</p>
<p>The TaylorMade Product Tester Program is an exciting opportunity for passionate golfers to play a part in the development of the latest golf equipment. If you’re a dedicated golfer with a passion for the sport and a desire to help shape the future of golf equipment, this program may be right for you.</p>
<p>Best Taylormade Product Tester Club</p>
<p>As a TaylorMade product tester, you have the unique opportunity to test and provide feedback on a wide range of golf equipment. From drivers to irons to putters, there are plenty of options to choose from. However, one of the most exciting products to test as a TaylorMade product tester is their latest driver.</p>
<p>TaylorMade has a long-standing reputation for producing some of the best drivers in the game of golf. Their drivers are known for their distance, accuracy, and forgiveness, making them a popular choice among golfers of all skill levels. As a product tester, you’ll have the chance to test out the latest TaylorMade driver models and provide feedback on their performance, design, and overall feel.</p>
<p>One driver model that may be particularly exciting for product testers to test is the SIM2 Max driver. This driver is designed with a larger sweet spot, allowing for more forgiveness on off-center hits. It also features a unique weight distribution system that helps to optimize launch and spin conditions, resulting in longer, straighter drives.</p>
<p>Another driver that may be of interest to product testers is the TaylorMade SIM2 driver. This driver is designed with a larger face and a unique sole design, resulting in increased ball speed and distance. It also features adjustable loft and lies settings, allowing golfers to fine-tune their launch conditions for maximum performance.</p>
<p><a target="_blank" href="https://kiiky.com/wealth/make-money-online-with-google/" rel="noreferrer noopener">Make Money Online with Google Products in 2023</a></p>
<p>Tips on How to Get Selected to be a Taylormade Product Tester</p>
<p>Being selected as a TaylorMade product tester is a coveted opportunity for avid golfers, but the selection process can be competitive. Here are some tips on how to increase your chances of being selected:</p>
<p>Be an avid golfer: TaylorMade is looking for passionate golfers who have experience using different types of golf equipment. The more you know about the game of golf and the equipment used, the better.</p>
<p> Have a strong social media presence: TaylorMade often looks for product testers who have a strong social media following. If you have an engaged audience on social media, it can demonstrate your ability to effectively communicate and provide feedback on new products.</p>
<p> Provide detailed and honest feedback: As a product tester, your main responsibility is to test the products and provide detailed feedback on their performance, design, and overall feel. Be sure to provide honest and thorough feedback, as this can increase your chances of being selected for future testing opportunities.</p>
<p> Apply for the program: TaylorMade often promotes its product testing program on its website and social media channels. Keep an eye out for application periods and apply for the program if you meet the requirements.</p>
<p> Attend TaylorMade events: Attending TaylorMade events and engaging with the brand can help you stand out as a potential product tester. It also demonstrates your dedication to the game of golf and the brand.</p>
<p>These steps can increase your chances of being selected as a TaylorMade product tester and have the opportunity to test out the latest golf equipment before it hits the market.</p>
<p>FAQs</p>
<p>How do I join Team TaylorMade? Team TaylorMade is an ambassador program that provides golfers with exclusive access to the brand’s latest equipment and events. To join, visit the TaylorMade website and apply to become an ambassador. The application typically requires providing your golfing background, social media channels, and why you want to join Team TaylorMade. If accepted, you’ll be provided with the latest equipment and opportunities to represent the brand at various events.  How do I know if my TaylorMade is real? To determine if your TaylorMade club is real, you can look for several indicators. Check the club head for authentic logos, markings, and serial numbers. The grip should also have the TaylorMade logo and feel secure. You can also compare the weight and measurements of your club to the official TaylorMade specifications to ensure they match.  Do any pros use TaylorMade? Yes, many professional golfers use TaylorMade equipment on the PGA Tour and other professional golf circuits. Some notable players who use TaylorMade equipment include Dustin Johnson, Rory McIlroy, Collin Morikawa, and Tiger Woods (when he was still competing). TaylorMade is a popular choice among professional golfers for its innovative technology, performance, and quality.  </p>
<p>Conclusion</p>
<p>Becoming a TaylorMade product tester is a unique opportunity for golf enthusiasts to try out the latest equipment and have a say in shaping future products. By following the tips outlined in this guide, such as being an avid golfer, providing detailed feedback, and having a strong social media presence, you can increase your chances of being selected as a product tester. Keep an eye out for application periods and attend TaylorMade events to further demonstrate your dedication to the brand.</p>
<p>References</p>
<p>Recommendations</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/how-to-become-a-taylormade-product-tester-in-2023-full-guide/">How to Become a Taylormade Product Tester in 2023 | Full Guide</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://us.yorba.org/how-to-become-a-taylormade-product-tester-in-2023-full-guide/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Conn Smythe odds: Jonathan Marchessault tops list to win playoff MVP</title>
		<link>http://us.yorba.org/conn-smythe-odds-jonathan-marchessault-tops-list-win-playoff-mvp/</link>
					<comments>http://us.yorba.org/conn-smythe-odds-jonathan-marchessault-tops-list-win-playoff-mvp/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[usyorba]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:56:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conn]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jonathan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[list]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marchessault]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MVP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[odds]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[playoff]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Smythe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tops]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[win]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://us.yorba.org/?p=104</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>May 12, 2023; Las Vegas, Nevada, USA; Vegas Golden Knights right wing Jonathan Marchessault (81) warms up before the start of game five of the second round of the 2023 Stanley Cup...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/conn-smythe-odds-jonathan-marchessault-tops-list-win-playoff-mvp/">Conn Smythe odds: Jonathan Marchessault tops list to win playoff MVP</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://images2.minutemediacdn.com/image/fetch/w_850,h_560,c_fill,g_auto,f_auto/https%3A%2F%2Ffansided.com%2Fwp-content%2Fuploads%2Fimagn-images%2F2023%2F06%2F20654564-850x560.jpeg" rel="attachment wp-att-2425421"/>May 12, 2023; Las Vegas, Nevada, USA; Vegas Golden Knights right wing Jonathan Marchessault (81) warms up before the start of game five of the second round of the 2023 Stanley Cup Playoffs against the Edmonton Oilers at T-Mobile Arena. Mandatory Credit: Stephen R. Sylvanie-USA TODAY Sports<a href="https://fansided.com/2023/06/06/aaron-judge-toe-injury-yankees/" rel="prev">Aaron Judge injury update: Things don’t look good for Yankees by Kristen Wong</a><a href="https://fansided.com/2023/06/06/lions-dan-campbell-jared-goff-improvement-sean-mcvay/" rel="next">Lions: Dan Campbell thinks Jared Goff has improved without Sean McVay by John Buhler</a>     The Vegas Golden Knights have taken over as a <a href="https://fansided.com/2023/06/06/golden-knights-stanley-cup-odds-skyrocket-game-2-win/" rel="">sizable favorite to win the Stanley Cup</a> after taking a 2-0 series lead over the Florida Panthers.As a result, the Conn Smythe Trophy odds have also shifted. The award is given to the MVP of the NHL Playoffs and it’s almost always given to a player belonging to the winning team. So, as you’d expect, players on the Golden Knights are starting to float to the top of the odds list.Let’s take a look at the latest odds to win the Conn Smythe heading into Game 3 in Florida.Conn Smythe Trophy oddsConn Smythe Trophy &#8211; 2022-23Odds updated June 6th, 2023, at 4:46 pmJonathan Marchessault is the new betting favorite to win the Conn Smythe Trophy at -105 odds, which is an implied probability of 51.22%.Marchessault has been hot in the playoffs dating back to the last round. He now has 21 points in 19 postseason games, including a three goals and an assist in the first two games against the Panthers.<a href="https://bit.ly/FanSided-Web-DraftKings" class="chakra-linkbox__overlay css-1cst4gr" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">DraftKings</a>New Users: Bet $5 on Any NHL Playoff Game, Get $200 in Bonus Bets Instantly!<a target="_blank" rel="noopener" class="chakra-link css-1hhai3c" href="https://bit.ly/FanSided-Web-DraftKings">New customers only. 21+ (18+ WY) and present in AZ, CO, CT, IL, IN, IA, KS, LA, MD, MI, NJ, NY, PA, TN, VA, WV, WY. All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements. See full terms at sportsbook.draftkings.com/footballterms. Valid 1 per new customer. Minimum $5 deposit and wager required. Rewards issued as non-withdrawable free bets or site credits (i.e. if your wager wins you receive a $200 bonus paid as 8 free bets of $25 each in addition to any cash winnings from original wager). Gambling Problem? Call/text 1-800-GAMBLER (IL/NJ/PA/WV), call/text 1-800-522-4700 (CO/KS/LA/WY), call 1-800-NEXT-STEP or text NEXTSTEP to 53342 (AZ), call 888-789-7777 or visit ccpg.org/chat (CT), call 1-800-BETS-OFF or visit yourlifeiowa.org/gambling (IA), call 1-800-9-WITH-IT or text INGAMB to 53342 (IN), call 1-800-270-7117 (MI), call (877-8-HOPENY) or text HOPENY (467369) (NY), call/text TN REDLINE 1-800-889-9789 (TN) or call/text 1-888-532-3500 (VA).</a>Read moreJack Eichel is second on the odds list, recording 22 points in the 19 games. With that being said, he only six of his points are goals. With goals held at a higher regard than assists, Marchessault has the edge with his 12 goals.The interesting dark horse is Adin Hill, the goaltender for the Golden Knights, at +500. He has quietly been phenomenal in the playoffs, sporting a 2.06 goals against average and a .937 save percentage in 13 games and 11 starts in the playoffs.The favorite at the start of the Stanley Cup Final, Sergei Bobrovsky, has fallen all the way to +1300 after two poor performances in the first two games. He was even pulled from the net in Game 2 after allowing four goals on just 13 shots.If the Golden Knights win Game 3, all Panthers on the odds list are going to continue to fall down the odds board.<a href="https://bit.ly/FanSided-Web-Caesars" class="chakra-linkbox__overlay css-1cst4gr" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Caesars</a>Get Your First Bet on Caesars up to $1,250 When You Bet Any NHL Game!<a target="_blank" rel="noopener" class="chakra-link css-1hhai3c" href="https://bit.ly/FanSided-Web-Caesars">21+ only. Offer valid and must be physically present in AZ, CO, IL, IN, IA, KS, LA, MI, NJ, NY, PA, TN, VA, WV &amp; WY only. New users and first $10+ wager only. Must register with eligible promo code. Bet amount of qualifying wager returned only if wager is settled as a loss. Maximum bet credit $1,250; must be used within 14 days of receipt. Tier Credits and Reward Credits will be added to account within 7 days after qualifying wager settles. Void where prohibited. Know When To Stop Before You Start® Gambling Problem? AZ: Call 1-800-NEXT-STEP; CO, WY, KS (Affiliated with Kansas Crossing Casino): Call 1-800-522-4700; IN: Call 1-800-9-WITH-IT; IA: Call 1-800-BETSOFF; LA: Call 1-877-770-STOP (licensed through Horseshoe Bossier City and Harrah’s New Orleans); MI: Call 1-800-270-7117; IL, NJ, VA, WV, PA (Affiliated with Harrah&#8217;s Philadelphia): If you or someone you know has a gambling problem, crisis counseling and referral services can be accessed by calling 1-800-GAMBLER (1-800-426-2537) or WV: visit 1800gambler.net. TN: Call or text TN REDLINE at 1-800-889-9789. ©2022, Caesars Entertainment. Gambling problem? Call 877-8-HOPENY or text HOPENY (467369). See Caesars.com/promos for full terms. Read More</a>Read more<a href="https://bit.ly/FanSided-Web-FanDuel" class="chakra-linkbox__overlay css-1cst4gr" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">FanDuel</a>Limited Time: Get a No Sweat First Bet up to $2,500 on the NHL Finals!<a target="_blank" rel="noopener" class="chakra-link css-1hhai3c" href="https://bit.ly/FanSided-Web-FanDuel">$10 first deposit required. Up to $2,500 back in free bets if you lose first online real money wager. New customers only. 21+ and present in AZ, CO, CT, IA, IL, IN, LA (permitted parishes only), MD, MI, NJ, NY, PA, TN, VA, WY, or WV. Restrictions apply. See full terms at sportsbook.fanduel.com. Gambling Problem? Call 1-800-GAMBLER (IL/MD/NJ/PA/WV) or visit mdgamblinghelp.org (MD), 1-800-522-4700 (CO/KS/WY), 1-800-NEXT-STEP or text NEXTSTEP to 53342 (AZ), 1-888-789-7777 or visit ccpg.org/chat (CT), 1-800-BETS-OFF (IA), 1-800-9-WITH-IT or text INGAMB to 53342 (IN), 1-877-770-STOP (LA), 1-800-270-7117 (MI), 1-877-8-HOPENY or text HOPENY (467369) (NY), TN REDLINE 1-800-889-9789 (TN), and 1-888-532-3500 (VA).</a>Read more–Game odds refresh periodically and are subject to change.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/conn-smythe-odds-jonathan-marchessault-tops-list-win-playoff-mvp/">Conn Smythe odds: Jonathan Marchessault tops list to win playoff MVP</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://us.yorba.org/conn-smythe-odds-jonathan-marchessault-tops-list-win-playoff-mvp/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Best Car Stereos (Updated 2023)</title>
		<link>http://us.yorba.org/best-car-stereos/</link>
					<comments>http://us.yorba.org/best-car-stereos/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[usyorba]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:56:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Movie]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Car]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stereos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Updated]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://us.yorba.org/?p=101</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Car stereos have come a long way from static-y AM radio to the infotainment hubs they are today. Car stereos have become one of the more important options to consider when purchasing...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/best-car-stereos/">Best Car Stereos (Updated 2023)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img decoding="async" src="https://static1.srcdn.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/CarStereo1.jpg" /><br />            Car stereos have come a long way from static-y AM radio to the infotainment hubs they are today. Car stereos have become one of the more important options to consider when purchasing a car or upgrading the existing setup in your vehicle. Smartphone integration is also a key factor, and with that evolution, car stereos have become more than just something that plays tunes while driving.<br />
                    Related: <a href="https://screenrant.com/best-car-gadgets/">The 10 Best Car Gadgets (Updated 2023)</a><br />
                    No longer just a mere accessory, car stereos must play and stream music in different formats, connect to our smartphones, navigate for us, and even play videos (while the car is parked). Some new vehicles have stereos that meet the needs of today’s drivers, but what about those situations where you are looking to replace a broken or upgrade an outdated car stereo? The choices are numerous and varied, just as with any other on-the-go infotainment needs. There are many things to consider when selecting a car stereo, and these are some of the best car stereos available.</p>
<p>                            Pioneer WT7600NEX</p>
<p>                    Best Overall Car Stereo</p>
<p>                    The Pioneer DMH-WT7600NEX is a feature-packed multi-media receiver with support for Apple CarPlay, Android Auto, and Alexa built-in.</p>
<p>                            Display<br />
                            9-inch LED touchscreen</p>
<p>                            Connectivity<br />
                            Bluetooth, USB</p>
<p>                            Internet Services<br />
                            SiriusXM-ready</p>
<p>                            Apple CarPlay<br />
                            Yes</p>
<p>                            Android Auto<br />
                            Yes</p>
<p>                            Brand<br />
                            Pioneer</p>
<p>                                            Pros</p>
<p>                                                            Apple CarPlay and Android Auto support<br />
                                                            Built-in HD radio tuner<br />
                                                            Large LED touchscreen</p>
<p>                                            Cons</p>
<p>                                                            Installation can be tricky<br />
                                                            Pricey</p>
<p>            The Pioneer DMH WT7600NEX is top-of-the-line when it comes to car stereos. More than just a car stereo, the WT7600NEX is a multimedia receiver for your car with a wide array of excellent features that enhance your driving experience. It is compatible with Apple CarPlay, Amazon Alexa, and Android Auto for seamless wired or wireless access to your favorite apps.<br />
                    There are also other music sources with the SiriusXM-ready device and a built-in HD radio tuner. It also features Bluetooth connectivity for hands-free calling and audio streaming. You don&#8217;t have to worry about compatibility with different types of smartphones and audio providers. Sound quality is also terrific thanks to a 13-band, customizable graphic equalizer and a built-in digital signal processor.<br />
                    While the WT7600NEX is a single DIN unit, it features a responsive, large, and vibrant 9-inch LED touchscreen with a floating design with horizontal, vertical, and tilt adjustability. Additional features include inputs for a backup and other cameras, USB input, a detachable face for security, and a remote control. The WT7600 may be at the high end in price, but its premium features and performance make it well worth it and one of the best overall.</p>
<p>                            Alpine Halo11 iLX-F511</p>
<p>                    Best Touchscreen</p>
<p>                    The Alpine Halo11 iLX-F511 has one of the best largest touchscreens on any car stereo today. The fantastic screen is backed by Apple CarPlay and Android Auto compatibility and excellent audio performance.</p>
<p>                            Display<br />
                            11-inch capacitive touchscreen</p>
<p>                            Connectivity<br />
                            Bluetooth, USB, HDMI, </p>
<p>                            Internet Services<br />
                            SiriusXM-ready</p>
<p>                            Apple CarPlay<br />
                            Yes</p>
<p>                            Android Auto<br />
                            Yes</p>
<p>                            Brand<br />
                            Alpine</p>
<p>                                            Pros</p>
<p>                                                            Adjustable 11-inch capacitive touchscreen<br />
                                                            Apple CarPlay and Android Auto compatibility<br />
                                                            HDMI input</p>
<p>                                            Cons</p>
<p>                                                            Screen may be too big for some cars<br />
                                                            Expensive<br />
                                                            Camera inputs only compatible with Alpine cameras</p>
<p>            The Alpine Halo11 iLX511 features the best touchscreen you can find on a car stereo. Measuring a gigantic 11-inch, the screen is floating with adjustability for height, depth, and viewing angle. The display resolution is eye-catching and crisp at 1280 x 720 pixels and is also very responsive. However, despite the size of the touchscreen, the iLX511 fits most single-DIN openings.<br />
                    More than just a pretty face, the iLX511 has excellent smartphone integration with compatibility for Android Auto and Apple CarPlay, along with Bluetooth connectivity for hands-free calling and audio streaming. It is also SiriusXM-ready and has a built-in HD radio. There are camera and USB inputs along with an HDMI connection for a CD/DVD or Blu-ray player. Unfortunately, the camera inputs are compatible only with Alpine cameras, though a composite video adapter for connecting a non-Alpine camera is included. Sound performance is excellent with adjustability via a 13-band parametric equalizer and high- and low-pass filters, among other audio enhancements.</p>
<p>                            Pioneer DMH-WC5700NEX</p>
<p>                    Best For Apple CarPlay</p>
<p>                    The Pioneer DMH-WC5700NEX is an excellent option for seamless integration with your iPhone and Apple CarPlay support. The 6.8-inch touchscreen is smartphone-sized and might be preferred by those that don&#8217;t want a large, floating display.</p>
<p>                            Display<br />
                            6.8-inch capacitive touchscreen</p>
<p>                            Connectivity<br />
                            Bluetooth, USB, Wi-Fi</p>
<p>                            Internet Services<br />
                            SiriusXM, Pandora, Spotify</p>
<p>                            Apple CarPlay<br />
                            Yes</p>
<p>                            Android Auto<br />
                            Yes</p>
<p>                            Brand<br />
                            Pioneer</p>
<p>                                            Pros</p>
<p>                                                            Touchscreen size is more manageable<br />
                                                            Built-in HD radio tuner<br />
                                                            Wired and wireless support for Apple CarPlay and Android Auto</p>
<p>                                            Cons</p>
<p>                                                            SiriusXM tuner not built-in</p>
<p>            The DMH-WC5700NEX is a modular car stereo featuring a 6.8-inch capacitive touchscreen and a single-DIN installation chassis. The tablet-like display features icon controls and is connected to the chassis via a cable that allows for versatile installation even in tight compartments. And being able to separate the display from the chassis gives the WC5700NEX a familiar and easy-to-use tablet-like feel.<br />
                    The WC5700NEX has outstanding wired or wireless support for Apple CarPlay, allowing easy and safe hands-free access to your phone including your music library, messages, and your favorite apps. It is also compatible with Android Auto and Amazon Alexa. Connectivity includes Bluetooth, Wi-Fi, HDMI, two camera inputs, and a rear AUX input. The built-in 50W x 4 amplifier provides plenty of power for the 13-band graphic equalizer to produce exceptional sound quality. If an iPhone is your smartphone of choice, the Pioneer DMH-WC5700NEX is one of the best when it comes to Apple CarPlay support.</p>
<p>                            Kenwood DMX908S</p>
<p>                    Best For Android Auto</p>
<p>                    The Kenwood DMX908S has excellent support for Android Auto for total integration with your Android phone. It is highlighted by a 6.9-inch touchscreen and top-notch car stereo features. </p>
<p>                            Display<br />
                            6.9-inch capacitive touchscreen</p>
<p>                            Connectivity<br />
                            Bluetooth, USB</p>
<p>                            Internet Services<br />
                            SiriusXM</p>
<p>                            Apple CarPlay<br />
                            Yes</p>
<p>                            Android Auto<br />
                            Yes</p>
<p>                            Brand<br />
                            Kenwood</p>
<p>                                            Pros</p>
<p>                                                            High-resolution 6.9-inch capacitive touchscreen<br />
                                                            Built-in HD radio tuner<br />
                                                            USB-C port</p>
<p>                                            Cons</p>
<p>                                                            Wireless screen mirroring only with select Android phones<br />
                                                            Display does not move</p>
<p>            The Kenwood DMX908S is the best Android Auto car stereo you can get. Seamless wired or wireless Android Auto integration means easy and safe access to calls, your music, weather, navigation, and more. An added bonus for Android users is wireless screen mirroring with select smartphones. Of course, the DMX908S is also Apple CarPlay compatible.<br />
                    Connectivity features include Bluetooth for hands-free calling and audio streaming, four camera inputs, SiriusXM-ready, and a built-in HD radio tuner. It&#8217;s also one of the few options to come with a USB-C port that provides fast charging for your Android device. The DMX908S is highlighted by a 6.9-inch capacitive LED-backlit LCD touchscreen. Sound performance is rich and immersive with a built-in amplifier, a 13-band graphic equalizer, and digital signal processing. If Android is your smartphone of choice, the Kenwood DMX908S is the car stereo to get.</p>
<p>                                    Alpine iLX-W650 car stereo from the front</p>
<p>                            Alpine iLX-W650</p>
<p>                    Best For Easy Installation</p>
<p>                    The Alpine iLX-W650 features a 7-inch touchscreen and supports Apple CarPlay and Android Auto. Its shallow chassis makes installation and expandability easy.</p>
<p>                            Display<br />
                            7-inch capacitive touchscreen</p>
<p>                            Connectivity<br />
                            Bluetooth, USB</p>
<p>                            Internet Services<br />
                            SiriusXM</p>
<p>                            Apple CarPlay<br />
                            Yes</p>
<p>                            Android Auto<br />
                            Yes</p>
<p>                            Brand<br />
                            Alpine</p>
<p>                                            Pros</p>
<p>                                                            Affordable<br />
                                                            Shallow mount design<br />
                                                            7-inch capacitive touchscreen<br />
                                                            Optional adapter adds steering wheel control</p>
<p>            The Alpine iLX-W650 is a double-DIN car stereo with a 7-inch capacitive touchscreen that makes controlling everything easy and intuitive. The head unit is compatible with Android Auto and Apple CarPlay, and connectivity comes via Bluetooth, two camera inputs, and USB. Other features include an external microphone for voice commands and hands-free phone use, with an optional adapter to add steering wheel control. The sound quality is superb with 50W x 4 power and a built-in amplifier.<br />
                    An outstanding feature is the size of the unit. The iLX-W650 has a shallow mount design at only 2-13/16 inches deep which makes installation easy, particularly if space is at a premium behind the dashboard in your car. The shallow design also leaves plenty of room for future expandability with other aftermarket accessories like a power pack amp. The Alpine iLX-W650 is not only one of the best for its ease of installation, but it also won’t break the bank.</p>
<p>                                    Kenwood eXcelon DDX396BT from the front</p>
<p>                            Kenwood Excelon DDX396BT</p>
<p>                    Best Car Stereo With A CD Player</p>
<p>                    The KENWOOD Excelon DDX396BT is one of the best car stereos to get if you also want to play music from CDs. Additional features include a 6.2-inch touchscreen and graphic equalizer.</p>
<p>                            Display<br />
                            6.2-inch resistive touchscreen</p>
<p>                            Connectivity<br />
                            Bluetooth, USB</p>
<p>                            Internet Services<br />
                            SiriusXM-ready</p>
<p>                            Apple CarPlay<br />
                            No</p>
<p>                            Android Auto<br />
                            No</p>
<p>                            Brand<br />
                            Kenwood</p>
<p>                                            Pros</p>
<p>                                                            Plays CDs and DVDs<br />
                                                            Affordable</p>
<p>                                            Cons</p>
<p>                                                            No support for Apple CarPlay or Android Auto<br />
                                                            Resistive touchscreen is not as smooth as capacitive options</p>
<p>            The KENWOOD Excelon DDX396BT is a double-DIN head unit with a 6.2-inch resistive touchscreen. Resistive touchscreens require firm taps and presses, so the inclusion of physical controls along the left side of the panel is a nice bonus. Connectivity includes USB and Bluetooth that supports Apple or Android smartphone connections and charging. However, it isn&#8217;t compatible with CarPlay or Android Auto.<br />
                    When it comes to audio streaming, the DDX396BT is capable of supporting five streaming devices simultaneously. The selling point, though, is its CD/DVD player for those who have held onto physical discs and supports a wide range of digital video and music formats. Sound quality is enhanced via a 13-band graphic equalizer and loudness control, among other settings. If you want to continue to enjoy your CDs on the road, the KENWOOD Excelon DDX396BT is the best available, putting digital and physical media at your fingertips.</p>
<p>                                    JVC Kw-M56BT car stereo from the front</p>
<p>                            JVC KW-M56BT Android Auto in-dash unit</p>
<p>                    Best Affordable Car Stereo</p>
<p>                    The JVC KW-M56BT car has all the features you&#8217;d expect from a modern car stereo like a capacitive touchscreen and Apple CarPlay and Android Auto support, but with a far more affordable price tag. </p>
<p>                            Display<br />
                            6.8-inch capacitive touchscreen</p>
<p>                            Connectivity<br />
                            Bluetooth, USB</p>
<p>                            Internet Services<br />
                            SiriusXM</p>
<p>                            Apple CarPlay<br />
                            Yes</p>
<p>                            Android Auto<br />
                            Yes</p>
<p>                            Brand<br />
                            JVC</p>
<p>                                            Pros</p>
<p>                                                            Affordable<br />
                                                            6.8-inch touchscreen with gesture control<br />
                                                            Apple CarPlay and Android Auto support</p>
<p>                                            Cons</p>
<p>                                                            SiriusXM tuner not built-in</p>
<p>            The JVC KW M56BT should be the go-to option for anyone looking for one of the best affordable car stereos. The M56BT is a double-DIN car stereo and features a customizable 6.8-inch capacitive touchscreen. Gesture control is a nice feature that brings easy volume and track control. The M56BT has top-notch sound performance thanks to the built-in amplifier and equalizer to back up its 50 watts of power per channel.<br />
                    Additional features that you would expect to find on much more expensive units include wired support for Apple CarPlay and Android Auto, hands-free calling via Bluetooth, and SiriusXM support. Also included are a backup camera input and steering wheel controls with an additional adapter. The JVC KW M56BT proves you don&#8217;t have to break the bank for a full-feature car stereo.</p>
<p>                            JVC KD-T920BTS</p>
<p>                    Best Single-DIN Car Stereo</p>
<p>                    The JVC KD-T920BTS is one of the best single-DIN car stereos available. It features Bluetooth and Amazon Alexa.</p>
<p>                            Display<br />
                            2 Line Vertical Alignment LCD</p>
<p>                            Connectivity<br />
                            Bluetooth, USB, AUX</p>
<p>                            Apple CarPlay<br />
                            No</p>
<p>                            Android Auto<br />
                            No</p>
<p>                            Brand<br />
                            JVC</p>
<p>                                            Pros</p>
<p>                                                            Plays CDs<br />
                                                            Detachable face<br />
                                                            Built-in Amazon Alexa</p>
<p>                                            Cons</p>
<p>                                                            No support for Apple CarPlay or Android Auto<br />
                                                            SiriusXM requires separate tuner</p>
<p>            There are a few single-DIN car stereos with touchscreens, but if you&#8217;re lacking space on your dash, the JVC KD-T920BTS is a good option to consider. The KD-T920BTS has a detachable 2-Line Vertical Alignment LCD display for great visibility and information. The display also features a customizable 2-zone variable-color button and accent illumination. Not only does it play CDs, but it is also SiriusXM-ready (with an optional tuner), has a front AUX input, and has a USB port for music on a thumb drive.<br />
                    The KD-T920BTS also features Bluetooth for hands-free calling and audio streaming for iPhone and Android phones. The JVC Streaming DJ feature allows for streaming and playback control from up to five paired smartphones. Sound quality is formidable with a 13-band equalizer and JVC&#8217;s K2 technology that improves the sound of CDs and digital music files. A nice feature is Amazon Alexa compatibility which is activated via a dedicated button on the front panel. The JVC KD-T920BTS is a quality single-DIN option and one of the best.</p>
<p>            Which Is The Best Car Stereo?<br />
                   There are many factors that go into what will be considered the best car stereo for you. These include whether the unit will fit in your car, the type of smartphone you have, and what type of music source you use, among others.<br />
                    The Pioneer WT7600NEX is our top pick because it combines a wide array of features and outstanding performance to enhance your driving experience. It&#8217;s a great choice for anyone who wants seamless smartphone integration with a car stereo. And the best part is that even though it has a large touchscreen, which is normally seen with double-DIN units, the WT7600 fits in a single-DIN slot.<br />
                    Speaking of installation, the Alpine iLX-W650 is worth getting for its shallow chassis, making it a good choice for car dashes that don&#8217;t have much real estate. Easy installation aside, it also offers excellent smartphone integration. If you&#8217;re looking to save some money, the JVC KW M56BT is the one to get. A lower price doesn&#8217;t mean a lack of features, though. The KW M56BT checks all the boxes you&#8217;d expect from a more expensive car stereo, including smartphone integration, top-notch sound, and gesture controls.</p>
<p>                            Pioneer WT7600NEX</p>
<p>                    Best Overall</p>
<p>                    The Pioneer DMH-WT7600NEX is a feature-packed multi-media receiver with support for Apple CarPlay, Android Auto, and Alexa built-in.</p>
<p>                            Display<br />
                            9-inch LED touchscreen</p>
<p>                            Connectivity<br />
                            Bluetooth, USB</p>
<p>                            Internet Services<br />
                            SiriusXM-ready</p>
<p>                            Apple CarPlay<br />
                            Yes</p>
<p>                            Android Auto<br />
                            Yes</p>
<p>                            Brand<br />
                            Pioneer</p>
<p>                                            Pros</p>
<p>                                                            Apple CarPlay and Android Auto support<br />
                                                            Built-in HD radio tuner<br />
                                                            Large LED touchscreen</p>
<p>                                            Cons</p>
<p>                                                            Installation can be tricky<br />
                                                            Pricey</p>
<p>            FAQs<br />
       Q: Is Apple CarPlay or Android Auto necessary if the car stereo has Bluetooth?            A: Bluetooth is not the same as Apple CarPlay or Android Auto. Bluetooth uses radio frequencies at short range to transfer data mainly for audio streaming and hands-free calling. Meanwhile, CarPlay and Android Auto offer more robust smartphone integration with easy access to a variety of apps for music streaming, messaging, navigation, and more. AC and AA can be connected to your car stereo either wired or wirelessly and are modeled in ways to safely utilize our smartphones while driving such as larger screens and the ability to use voice assistants (Siri and Google Assistant).<br />
        Q: How will I know if a car stereo will fit in my car? Double-DIN vs Singe-DIN.            A: Not all car stereos are compatible with all cars. There are primarily two form factors when it comes to car stereos, single and double-DIN. DIN stands for Deutsche Industrie Norm which is the standardized car stereo opening size for cars. This standard has two sizes, single-DIN, which is roughly two inches tall and 7 inches wide, and double-DIN, which is around four inches wide and seven inches tall.<br />
                    One of the main differences is that a double-DIN slot will let you install a stereo with a large display or touchscreen. However, there are an increasing number of car stereos with modular or floating screens which means you can have a large display even with a single-DIN unit.<br />
        Q: Do call car stereos play all music formats?            A: Modern car stereos offer many options when it comes to music playback. Most car stereos are compatible with digital formats like MP3, AAC, and WMA and will play those formats from a variety of sources. Digital music can be played via streaming, from a USB thumb drive, input to an AUX port, and more. While digital media is becoming the norm, some car stereos can still play CDs and even DVDs depending on the unit.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/best-car-stereos/">Best Car Stereos (Updated 2023)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://us.yorba.org/best-car-stereos/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Become a Jordan Product Tester in 2023 &#124; Full Guide</title>
		<link>http://us.yorba.org/jordan-product-tester/</link>
					<comments>http://us.yorba.org/jordan-product-tester/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[usyorba]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:54:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Full]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guide]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jordan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Product]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tester]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://us.yorba.org/?p=98</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Are you a sneaker enthusiast with a passion for the iconic Jordan brand? Have you ever dreamed of becoming a product tester for Jordan and contributing to the development of new designs...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/jordan-product-tester/">How to Become a Jordan Product Tester in 2023 | Full Guide</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p>
<p>Are you a sneaker enthusiast with a passion for the iconic Jordan brand? Have you ever dreamed of becoming a product tester for Jordan and contributing to the development of new designs and technologies? Well, you’re in luck! In this guide, we will walk you through the steps required to become a Jordan product tester in 2023.</p>
<p>Becoming a Jordan product tester is a dream job for many, and it’s easy to see why. As a product tester, you get to try out new designs and technologies before they hit the market, providing valuable feedback to the Jordan team and helping to shape the future of the brand.</p>
<p>In this guide, we’ll cover everything you need to know about becoming a Jordan product tester. We’ll explore the qualifications required, the application process, and what you can expect from the job. We’ll also provide tips and advice on how to increase your chances of being selected as a product tester.</p>
<p>It doesn’t matter if you’re a seasoned sneakerhead or just starting your journey, this guide will provide you with the information you need to pursue your dream of becoming a Jordan product tester in 2023. So, if you’re ready to take your passion for sneakers to the next level and become an integral part of the Jordan team, let’s get started!</p>
<p>Who is a Jordan Product Tester?</p>
<p>A Jordan product tester is a person who is responsible for testing new Jordan products, including sneakers and apparel, before they are released to the public. They provide valuable feedback to the Jordan team, helping to ensure that the products meet the highest standards of quality, comfort, and performance.</p>
<p>As a product tester, you’ll get the chance to try out new designs and technologies and provide your input on what works well and what needs improvement. You’ll also be responsible for identifying any issues with the product and providing suggestions for how to fix them.</p>
<p>To become a Jordan product tester, you’ll need to have a deep knowledge and passion for sneakers, as well as an eye for detail and a willingness to provide honest and constructive feedback. You’ll also need to have strong communication skills, as you’ll be working closely with the Jordan team to provide your insights and suggestions.</p>
<p>Being a Jordan product tester is a dream job for many sneaker enthusiasts, and it’s easy to see why. Not only do you get to be at the forefront of new designs and technologies, but you also get to play a critical role in shaping the future of the brand. If you’re passionate about sneakers and want to contribute to the development of new products, becoming a Jordan product tester may be the perfect job for you.</p>
<p>Read: <a target="_blank" href="https://kiiky.com/wealth/how-to-become-a-taylormade-product-tester-in-2023-full-guide/" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Become a Taylormade Product Tester in 2023 | Full Guide</a></p>
<p>Why Does Jordan Hire Product Testers?</p>
<p>Jordan hires product testers to ensure that their products meet the highest standards of quality, comfort, and performance. By testing their products before they are released to the public, Jordan can identify any issues or areas for improvement and make the necessary changes to ensure that their products meet their customers’ needs and expectations.</p>
<p>Product testers provide valuable feedback to the Jordan team, including information on how the products fit, how comfortable they are, and how well they perform. This feedback is used to make adjustments to the design and manufacturing process, ensuring that the final product is the best it can be.</p>
<p>Moreover, Jordan hires product testers to maintain their reputation as one of the leading brands in the sneaker industry. By constantly innovating and improving their products, Jordan can stay ahead of the competition and maintain their loyal customer base.</p>
<p>In addition, hiring product testers helps Jordan stay connected to their customers and understand their needs and preferences better. This information is crucial for the brand to continue producing products that meet the evolving demands of its customers.</p>
<p>Hiring product testers is a crucial step in the product development process for Jordan, allowing them to create high-quality products that meet the needs of their customers and maintain their position as a leading brand in the sneaker industry.</p>
<p>Is Jordan Product Tester Legit?</p>
<p>Yes, Jordan product tester is a legitimate job opportunity for sneaker enthusiasts who are passionate about the brand and its products. As one of the leading brands in the sneaker industry, Jordan places great importance on ensuring that their products meet the highest standards of quality, comfort, and performance.</p>
<p>To achieve this, Jordan hires product testers to provide valuable feedback on their products before they are released to the public. Product testers play a critical role in the development process, ensuring that the final product meets the needs and expectations of customers.</p>
<p>If you’re interested in becoming a Jordan product tester, it’s important to do your research and ensure that you’re applying through legitimate channels. Jordan typically advertises job openings on their website or through reputable job search platforms.</p>
<p>Becoming a Jordan product tester is a legitimate opportunity for sneaker enthusiasts who are passionate about the brand and want to contribute to its success.</p>
<p>What are the Eligibility Requirements for Jordan Product Tester?</p>
<p>To become a Jordan product tester, there are certain eligibility requirements that you must meet. While the specific requirements may vary depending on the position and location, here are some of the common requirements you can expect:</p>
<p>Age: Typically, Jordan product testers must be at least 18 years of age or older.</p>
<p> Expertise: You should have deep knowledge and passion for sneakers, specifically the Jordan brand. You should have a keen eye for detail and be able to provide honest and constructive feedback on product design and performance.</p>
<p> Availability: As a product tester, you’ll need to be available to work flexible hours, including evenings and weekends. You’ll also need to be able to travel as required for testing and research purposes.</p>
<p> Communication Skills: You’ll need to have strong communication skills, including the ability to provide clear and concise feedback both verbally and in writing.</p>
<p> Legal eligibility: You must be legally eligible to work in the country or region where the position is located.</p>
<p>In addition to these eligibility requirements, Jordan may also require product testers to have a certain level of education, experience, or specific skill sets. It’s important to carefully review the job description and qualifications before applying to ensure that you meet the requirements.</p>
<p>Also, read: <a target="_blank" href="https://kiiky.com/wealth/philips-product-tester/" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to Become a Philips Product Tester in 2023 | Full Guide</a></p>
<p>How to Become a Jordan Product Tester</p>
<p>If you’re a sneaker enthusiast who’s passionate about the Jordan brand and wants to contribute to the development of their products, becoming a Jordan product tester may be the perfect job for you. Here’s a step-by-step guide on how to apply:</p>
<p>Research the Position</p>
<p>Visit the official Jordan website or reputable job search platforms to find out if there are any current openings for product testers. Carefully read the job description and qualifications to ensure that you meet the requirements.</p>
<p>Prepare Your Application</p>
<p>Once you’ve found an opening, prepare your application materials. This may include your resume, cover letter, and any relevant work samples or portfolios.</p>
<p>Submit Your Application</p>
<p>Submit your application materials through the designated application channel, whether it’s through the Jordan website or a job search platform. Make sure to follow the instructions carefully and provide all the required information.</p>
<p>Participate in the Interview Process</p>
<p>If your application is selected, you’ll be invited to participate in the interview process. This may include phone or video interviews, as well as in-person interviews or product testing sessions.</p>
<p>Complete the Onboarding Process</p>
<p>If you’re selected for the position, you’ll need to complete the onboarding process, which may include background checks, signing an employment contract, and completing any necessary training.</p>
<p>Know that Jordan product tester positions may be highly competitive, so it’s essential to showcase your passion for the brand and your expertise in sneakers. Additionally, it’s important to be honest and constructive in your feedback during the product testing process, as this will help ensure that Jordan continues to produce high-quality products.</p>
<p>Do Jordan Product Testers Get Paid?</p>
<p>Yes, Jordan product testers are typically paid for their work. The specific compensation and benefits package may vary depending on the position, location, and company policies. However, as a product tester, you can expect to receive a competitive salary and benefits package that may include health insurance, retirement plans, and paid time off.</p>
<p>In addition to monetary compensation, being a Jordan product tester can provide valuable networking opportunities and exposure to industry professionals. It can also be a rewarding experience for sneaker enthusiasts who are passionate about the brand and want to contribute to its success.</p>
<p>It’s important to note that while being a Jordan product tester may be a fun and exciting job, it also comes with significant responsibilities. Product testers must provide honest and constructive feedback to ensure that the final product meets the needs and expectations of customers. By doing so, product testers play a critical role in maintaining the quality and reputation of the Jordan brand.</p>
<p>Are There Available Jordan Product Tester Jobs?</p>
<p>There are various Jordan product tester jobs available for those who are passionate about sneakers and the Jordan brand. Here are six potential positions and some information on their pay and salary:</p>
<p>Footwear Product Tester</p>
<p>As a footwear product tester, your job would be to test and provide feedback on new Jordan shoes and designs. The average salary for a footwear product tester is around $60,000 per year, but it can vary depending on experience and location.</p>
<p>Apparel Product Tester</p>
<p>In this role, you would be responsible for testing and providing feedback on Jordan apparel, including clothing and accessories. The average salary for an apparel product tester is around $55,000 per year.</p>
<p>Performance Tester</p>
<p>Performance testers focus on testing the performance of Jordan products, including how they hold up during various activities and sports. The average salary for a performance tester is around $70,000 per year.</p>
<p>Design Evaluator</p>
<p>Design evaluators are responsible for providing feedback on the design and aesthetics of new Jordan products. They ensure that the products are not only functional but also visually appealing to consumers. The average salary for a design evaluator is around $75,000 per year.</p>
<p>Quality Assurance Tester</p>
<p>Quality assurance testers are responsible for ensuring that Jordan products meet the brand’s high standards for quality. They test and evaluate products to identify any potential defects or issues before they reach consumers. The average salary for a quality assurance tester is around $65,000 per year.</p>
<p>Brand Ambassador</p>
<p>As a Jordan brand ambassador, you would be responsible for promoting the brand and its products to consumers. This can include attending events, creating social media content, and interacting with customers. The average salary for a brand ambassador is around $50,000 per year.</p>
<p>A Jordan product tester salary can vary based on several factors, including experience, location, and level of education. Additionally, Jordan may offer other benefits, such as health insurance, retirement plans, and paid time off.</p>
<p>While the pay and salary for Jordan product testers can be competitive, it’s important to remember that these jobs can also be highly competitive. Jordan may receive many applications for each position, so it’s important to showcase your passion for the brand and your expertise in the field.</p>
<p>By doing so, you can increase your chances of being selected for a Jordan product tester job and enjoy a rewarding career in the sneaker industry.</p>
<p>Also, see: <a target="_blank" href="https://kiiky.com/wealth/american-consumer-panels/" rel="noreferrer noopener">American Consumer Panels 2023: A New Product Testing Scam.</a></p>
<p>Can I Become a Jordan Product Tester from Home?</p>
<p>It is possible to become a Jordan product tester from home, but it may depend on the specific job requirements and location. In some cases, Jordan may offer remote product testing opportunities that allow testers to provide feedback on products from the comfort of their own homes.</p>
<p>However, some product testing jobs may require you to be physically present in a lab or testing facility to properly evaluate the product. For example, footwear testers may need to test the shoes on various surfaces and environments to accurately evaluate their performance.</p>
<p>It’s also important to note that remote product testing jobs may be highly competitive, as they offer the convenience of working from home while still contributing to the development of Jordan products.</p>
<p>If you’re interested in pursuing a remote product testing job with Jordan, it’s important to research job listings and reaches out to the company directly to learn more about their remote opportunities and application requirements.</p>
<p>What is the Average Salary for a Product Tester?</p>
<p>The average salary for a product tester can vary depending on the industry and specific job requirements. According to Glassdoor and Salary.com in 2023, the average salary for a product tester ranges from $45,000 to $85,000 per year, with some positions offering even higher salaries.</p>
<p>Factors that can affect a product tester’s salary include their level of experience, job location, and the industry they work in. For example, product testers in the technology industry may earn a higher salary than those in the food industry due to the complexity and demand of the products being tested.</p>
<p>It’s important to note that salaries for product testers can also vary based on the specific company and job position. Some companies may offer additional benefits such as health insurance, retirement plans, and bonuses, which can further increase a product tester’s overall compensation.</p>
<p>If you’re interested in pursuing a career as a product tester, it’s important to research job listings and company information to understand the average salary for the industry and the job position you’re interested in. By doing so, you can better prepare for your job search and negotiate a competitive salary once you’ve been offered a position.</p>
<p>Product Tester Program</p>
<p>A product tester program is a valuable opportunity for individuals interested in testing and evaluating products before they are released to the market. This program allows companies to receive feedback on their products from real consumers, which helps them improve product performance and overall customer satisfaction.</p>
<p>Product tester programs typically involve individuals signing up and receiving products to test and evaluate. Testers will then provide feedback to the company on their experience with the product, including any issues they encountered and suggestions for improvement.</p>
<p>For companies like Jordan, product tester programs are especially important as they strive to create high-quality products that meet the needs and preferences of their customers. By receiving feedback directly from consumers, Jordan can make informed decisions about product design, features, and marketing.</p>
<p>Participating in a product tester program can also be a rewarding experience for individuals who enjoy trying out new products and providing feedback. Testers often receive compensation for their time and effort, which can include free products, gift cards, or even payment.</p>
<p>If you’re interested in becoming a product tester, it’s important to research opportunities available in your industry and reach out to companies directly to learn more about their product tester programs and application requirements.</p>
<p>Best Product Tester Club</p>
<p>There are many product tester clubs available online that offer opportunities to test and review products from a variety of companies. These clubs are a great way for individuals to receive free products and provide feedback on their experiences, all while potentially earning compensation for their time and effort.</p>
<p>One of the best product tester clubs is the Amazon Vine program. This program is exclusive to Amazon and offers members the opportunity to receive free products in exchange for honest reviews. Members are selected based on their reviewer rank and helpfulness and are chosen to test products in a variety of categories including electronics, beauty, and household goods.</p>
<p>Another popular product tester club is Influenster. This program offers members free products from a variety of brands in exchange for social media posts and reviews. Members can also participate in surveys and polls to provide feedback to brands and earn rewards.</p>
<p>Other product tester clubs include PinchMe, which offers members free samples in exchange for reviews, and BzzAgent, which provides members with products to test and share with their social networks.</p>
<p>Participating in a product tester club can be a fun and rewarding experience for those who enjoy trying out new products and providing feedback. It’s important to research different clubs and their requirements before signing up and to always provide honest and thorough feedback to maintain credibility as a product tester.</p>
<p>Also, see- <a target="_blank" href="https://kiiky.com/wealth/11-platforms-you-can-get-paid-to-test-products-from-home/" rel="noreferrer noopener">11 Platforms You Can Get Paid To Test Products From Home in 2023</a></p>
<p>Tips on How to Get Selected to be a Product Tester</p>
<p>If you’re interested in becoming a product tester, there are several things you can do to increase your chances of being selected. Here are some tips on how to get selected to be a product tester:</p>
<p>Sign up for product tester programs</p>
<p>One of the easiest ways to become a product tester is to sign up for programs that are specifically designed for this purpose. Many companies have product tester programs, so look for opportunities in your industry of interest.</p>
<p>Build a strong online presence</p>
<p>Many product tester programs select testers based on their online presence and influence. Build a strong online presence on social media platforms like Instagram, Twitter, and YouTube to showcase your interests and expertise.</p>
<p>Engage with brands</p>
<p>Engage with the brands you’re interested in on social media by liking, commenting, and sharing their posts. This will help you build a relationship with the brand and potentially increase your chances of being selected as a product tester.</p>
<p>Write thorough and thoughtful reviews</p>
<p>If you’ve received products to test and review, make sure to provide detailed and thoughtful feedback. Brands want honest and thorough feedback from their testers, so take the time to thoroughly test the product and provide a detailed review.</p>
<p>Focus on your expertise</p>
<p>Many product tester programs are looking for testers with specific expertise or interests. Focus on your niche and expertise to increase your chances of being selected for relevant testing opportunities.</p>
<p>Stay active</p>
<p>Keep your online presence active and engage with brands regularly. This will show that you’re a reliable and engaged tester who is committed to providing valuable feedback.</p>
<p>Be professional</p>
<p>When communicating with brands or participating in product testing programs, be professional and courteous. Brands are looking for testers who are reliable and easy to work with, so be sure to respond promptly to emails and follow all instructions and guidelines.</p>
<p>Network with other product testers</p>
<p>Connect with other product testers in your industry to learn about new opportunities and share tips and advice. Networking with other testers can also help you build your online presence and increase your visibility to brands.</p>
<p>Apply to multiple programs</p>
<p>To increase your chances of being selected as a product tester, apply to multiple programs and opportunities. The more programs you apply to, the more likely you are to receive testing opportunities.</p>
<p>Becoming a product tester requires dedication, expertise, and professionalism. By following these tips and actively engaging with brands and other testers, you can increase your chances of being selected for product testing opportunities and build a successful career as a product tester.</p>
<p>FAQs</p>
<p>Are Jordan and Nike the same brand? Yes, Jordan is a sub-brand of Nike. It was created in collaboration with basketball legend Michael Jordan and features a range of athletic footwear, apparel, and accessories inspired by his legacy.  How do I become a product tester? To become a product tester, you can apply to specific companies’ testing programs or sign up for product testing websites. Make sure to meet eligibility requirements, fill out applications accurately, and provide detailed feedback during testing.  Do Nike testers get paid? Yes, Nike product testers do get paid for their participation in testing programs. The amount of compensation varies depending on the specific program and the product being tested.  </p>
<p>Conclusion</p>
<p>Becoming a product tester can be a rewarding and lucrative career path. With the right approach, expertise, and dedication, you can increase your chances of being selected for testing opportunities and building a successful career in this field. By following the tips outlined in this guide, you can position yourself as a top candidate for product testing programs and increase your chances of success in this exciting industry.</p>
<p>References</p>
<p>Recommendations</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/jordan-product-tester/">How to Become a Jordan Product Tester in 2023 | Full Guide</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://us.yorba.org/jordan-product-tester/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lions: Dan Campbell thinks Jared Goff has improved without Sean McVay</title>
		<link>http://us.yorba.org/lions-dan-campbell-jared-goff-improvement-sean-mcvay/</link>
					<comments>http://us.yorba.org/lions-dan-campbell-jared-goff-improvement-sean-mcvay/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[usyorba]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:54:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Campbell]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Goff]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[improved]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jared]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[McVay]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sean]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[thinks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://us.yorba.org/?p=95</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Dan Campbell believes Jared Goff is a better quarterback for him than he was playing for Sean McVay’s Los Angeles Rams.Look at Dan Campbell driving the Jared Goff hype train, man!Together, the...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/lions-dan-campbell-jared-goff-improvement-sean-mcvay/">Lions: Dan Campbell thinks Jared Goff has improved without Sean McVay</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p> Dan Campbell believes Jared Goff is a better quarterback for him than he was playing for Sean McVay’s Los Angeles Rams.Look at Dan Campbell driving the Jared Goff hype train, man!Together, the <a href="http://fansided.com/nfl/teams/detroit-lions">Detroit Lions</a> are well on their way towards building something special. After narrowly missing out on the NFC playoffs a year ago, one could argue that Detroit is the favorite to come out of the NFC North this season. A big reason for that has been the play of Goff. Campbell went as far to say Goff is a better quarterback now than with the Sean McVay <a href="http://fansided.com/nfl/teams/los-angeles-rams">Los Angeles Rams</a>.While I’m sure a lot of it has to do working with offensive coordinator Ben Johnson and quarterbacks coach Mark Brunell, it’s not like Goff was a scrub coming out of Cal. He played for Sonny Dykes and was the No. 1 overall pick by the Rams in the 2016 <a href="http://fansided.com/nfl/nfl-draft">NFL Draft</a> for a reason!Here is what Campbell had to say at the podium on Tuesday when speaking with the media.“His confidence has really grown … he’s a better quarterback than he was [in L.A.], in my opinion… we’ve come lightyears ahead of where he was two years ago when we started teaching him protections.”This is the entire clip of Campbell speaking with the Lions media about Goff and other big topics.The best part is the Lions are finally pulling in the same direction. It had been a while, to be honest.Dan Campbell feels Jared Goff is a better quarterback now with the Detroit LionsLook. I love everything about this comment from Campbell. It is fantastic. Goff always had talent. I remember watching him sling the pill around for Cal when the Golden Bears weren’t the least bit good and I thought to myself, “Oh, there is something here for sure!” Unfortunately, he played for the worst offenses of my lifetime on the 2016 Rams for Jeff Fisher. That would’ve ruined anyone.After not knowing where the sun went, Goff emerged as a Pro Bowl-caliber passer for the Rams for the next four years. Sadly, it wasn’t good enough for McVay, so he convinced owner Stan Kroenke to trade for fellow Georgia boy Matthew Stafford. Together, McVay and Stafford won a <a href="http://fansided.com/nfl/super-bowl">Super Bowl</a>. While the Lions stunk two years ago, they have the better ceiling … because of Goff.Yes, Detroit may have drafted Hendon Hooker out of Tennessee, but I am nowhere near as high on him as I was Goff coming out of Cal. He may be the future of Lions football, or he may just be a backup. Regardless, look for Goff to continue to grow in Johnson’s offense for as long as he remains in Detroit, as well as build on his rapport with Johnson’s potential successor in Brunell.See, Goff throws a beautiful spiral, but does need a savvy offensive mind to set him up for success to make plays down the field. In time, Goff will grow and mature into his late 20s, now that the cerebral part of his game has caught up to his natural gifts as a passer. Either way, I don’t think we’ve seen the best football out of Goff yet. He is why I am so excited about this Lions this season.If Goff plays up to his standard, Detroit could become one of the eight best teams in all of football. </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/lions-dan-campbell-jared-goff-improvement-sean-mcvay/">Lions: Dan Campbell thinks Jared Goff has improved without Sean McVay</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://us.yorba.org/lions-dan-campbell-jared-goff-improvement-sean-mcvay/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>WNBA Week Three: 3 must-see matchups this week</title>
		<link>http://us.yorba.org/wnba-power-rankings-3-best-games-week-3/</link>
					<comments>http://us.yorba.org/wnba-power-rankings-3-best-games-week-3/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[usyorba]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:53:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[matchups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mustsee]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Week]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[WNBA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://us.yorba.org/?p=92</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The WNBA has a full slate of games this week. Which matchups should be at the top of your viewing list?The WNBA season is in full swing and entering week three of...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/wnba-power-rankings-3-best-games-week-3/">WNBA Week Three: 3 must-see matchups this week</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p> The WNBA has a full slate of games this week. Which matchups should be at the top of your viewing list?The <a href="http://fansided.com/wnba/">WNBA</a> season is in full swing and entering week three of action. Awards races are starting to shape up. All-Star <a href="https://twitter.com/alfcorriette/status/1665781517925187585">voting starts tomorrow</a>.With storylines developing across the league, it can be overwhelming to keep up with what’s going on where. With consistent schedule overlap, it can be even more difficult choosing which games to watch.Allow us to help you decide. Here are three must-see games from this week’s WNBA slate.WNBA must-see games this week, June 5-June 12Las Vegas Aces at Connecticut Sun, June 6, 7 p.m. ESTWhere to watch: WNBA League Pass, NBC Sports Boston, Fox 5, SSSENA rematch of last year’s Finals, this might be the most anticipated game of the year, so far. The best part? These two teams also play on Thursday, Jun 8.Once again, this is matchup of the best two teams in the league. The Aces are the lone undefeated team remaining, while the Sun are right behind them at 6-1. The game features <a href="https://fansided.com/2023/06/06/wnba-mvp-ladder-alyssa-thomas-jackie-young/">two current MVP candidates</a> and will be a fun battle of styles. The Aces lead the league in field goal percentage, and hold their opponents to the lowest shooting percentage. The Sun hold opponents to the worst three-point shooting percentage, and have the third-best scoring defense in the league.Despite the familiarity, neither team is the same as the last time they met. The Sun have a new coach, system, and largely new roster. The Aces have much-improved depth, and an improved starting five (shoutout to Candace Parker).Chicago Sky at Los Angeles Sparks, June 9, 10 p.m. ESTWhere to watch: IonTV, WNBA League PassA battle of two scrappy teams who are outperforming expectations, this one should be a fun watch. Plus, it will be Azurá Stevens’ first game against her former team.ROSTER UPDATE: The Los Angeles Sparks announced today that Azurá Stevens has been activated ahead of Tuesday’s game against the Seattle Storm. Full Release: <a href="https://t.co/OiU9fxrzgm">https://t.co/OiU9fxrzgm</a>— LA Sparks PR (@LASparksPR) <a href="https://twitter.com/LASparksPR/status/1665900599324602368?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 6, 2023</a>The Sparks have established a new identity under Curt Miller, while the Sky have doubled down on theirs under James Wade. Both like to play with pace, and have their own quirks that make them interesting.The Sparks are the league’s best at forcing turnovers. The Sky commit the second-most turnovers. Both teams are top three in three-point shooting and top four in assists. This could turn into a high-scoring affair.Phoenix Mercury @ Indiana Fever, June 11, 5 p.m. ESTWhere to watch: CBS Sports, Facebook, IndianaFever, AZ Family 3TV, AZ Family Sports Network 44Five words describe the intrigue in this one: Aliyah Boston versus Brittney Griner. This season’s No. 1 pick will face off against one of the best to ever do it in what will be her (literal) biggest matchup so far.This is also a matchup of two teams in similar spots in the rankings, but vastly different paths there. The Mercury are a veteran team that have been showing their age in a bad way. They have some bad losses against teams they were expected to be better than. Meanwhile, the Fever are a young team showing theirs in the best ways possible. They have played some great, competitive games against some of the league’s best teams.The stylistic matchup is interesting, too. The Fever are the league’s third-best rebounding team, while the Mercury are last. The Mercury also average the most turnovers in the league by a sizable margin, averaging 6.5 more than the Fever do. Still, the Mercury shoot 46 percent from the field, second best in the league, to the Fever’s 40.4, which is tenth. The teams are the top two fouling teams in the league, though, which could be a big factor in this one. <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/wnba-power-rankings-3-best-games-week-3/">WNBA Week Three: 3 must-see matchups this week</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://us.yorba.org/wnba-power-rankings-3-best-games-week-3/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>New Mission: Impossible 7 Teaser Shows Closer Look At Tom Cruise&#039;s Train Stunt</title>
		<link>http://us.yorba.org/mission-impossible-7-trailer-tom-cruise-train-stunt/</link>
					<comments>http://us.yorba.org/mission-impossible-7-trailer-tom-cruise-train-stunt/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[usyorba]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:52:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Movie]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Closer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cruise039s]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impossible]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mission]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shows]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stunt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaser]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tom]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Train]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://us.yorba.org/?p=89</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A new teaser trailer for Mission: Impossible &#8211; Dead Reckoning Part One offers a closer look at a train stunt Tom Cruise does in the movie. Mission: Impossible &#8211; Dead Reckoning Part...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/mission-impossible-7-trailer-tom-cruise-train-stunt/">New Mission: Impossible 7 Teaser Shows Closer Look At Tom Cruise&#039;s Train Stunt</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img decoding="async" src="https://static1.srcdn.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/screen-shot-2023-06-06-at-5-45-40-pm.jpg" /><br />
A new teaser trailer for <a href="https://screenrant.com/tag/mission-impossible-7/">Mission: Impossible &#8211; Dead Reckoning Part One</a> offers a closer look at a train stunt Tom Cruise does in the movie. Mission: Impossible &#8211; Dead Reckoning Part One will be the first of a two-part finale for Cruise&#8217;s Ethan Hunt in the Mission: Impossible franchise. The film releases in theaters on July 12, 2023, with promises of plenty of action to kickstart the end of Ethan&#8217;s missions for the IMF.</p>
<p>Now, the <a href="https://twitter.com/MissionFilm/status/1666159103872487424" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Mission: Impossible</a> Twitter page has released a new teaser for <a href="https://screenrant.com/mission-impossible-7-release-date-cast-story-details/">Mission: Impossible &#8211; Dead Reckoning Part One</a>.<br />
SCREENRANT VIDEO OF THE DAYSCROLL TO CONTINUE WITH CONTENT</p>
<p>The short trailer shows off the many action sequences of the film, including a closer look at Cruise hanging onto a train. The end of the trailer sees Cruise&#8217;s face pressed against the top of the train, in what is no doubt another impressive stunt in the film.</p>
<p> The Many Impressive Stunts Of Mission: Impossible 7 </p>
<p>Cruise&#8217;s train stunt is one of many impressive action sequences that will be featured in Mission: Impossible &#8211; Dead Reckoning Part One. One of <a href="https://screenrant.com/mission-imposible-7-tom-cruise-stunt-risk-motorcycle/">Cruise&#8217;s death-defying Mission: Impossible 7 stunts</a> is when he rides a motorcycle off a cliff, jumping off it midair, and falling to the ground below. This stunt was done practically by Cruise, showcasing his dedication to making Mission: Impossible &#8211; Dead Reckoning Part One as authentic an action movie experience as possible.</p>
<p>However, that doesn&#8217;t mean the latest installment in the Mission: Impossible series hasn&#8217;t seen its fair share of difficulties. Production on the film began in February 2020, shutting down only a month later due to the worldwide COVID-19 pandemic. The film is also facing some theatrical difficulties as well, with reporting indicating <a href="https://screenrant.com/tom-cruise-mission-impossible-7-barbie-oppenheimer-imax-screens/">Cruise is angry at Oppenheimer and Barbie</a> for taking screens, such as IMAX screens, away from Mission: Impossible &#8211; Dead Reckoning Part One.</p>
<p>Despite the number of challenges the latest Mission: Impossible has faced, it&#8217;s clear Cruise has given his two-part finale all of his dedication, which will no doubt translate into an exciting film. The closer look at his train stunt in the movie underscores just how intense and thrilling the finale of Mission: Impossible will be. It remains to be seen if the final movie, which comes out in 2024, can compare to the excitement promised in Mission: Impossible &#8211; Dead Reckoning: Part One.</p>
<p>Source: <a href="https://twitter.com/MissionFilm/status/1666159103872487424" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Mission: Impossible</a>/Twitter</p>
<p>  Key Release Dates  <a title="Mission: Impossible - Dead Reckoning Part One" href="https://screenrant.com/tag/mission-impossible-7/">              Mission: Impossible &#8211; Dead Reckoning Part One  </a>   <a title="Mission: Impossible - Dead Reckoning - Part Two" href="https://screenrant.com/tag/mission-impossible-8/">              Mission: Impossible &#8211; Dead Reckoning &#8211; Part Two  </a>  <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/mission-impossible-7-trailer-tom-cruise-train-stunt/">New Mission: Impossible 7 Teaser Shows Closer Look At Tom Cruise&#039;s Train Stunt</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://us.yorba.org/mission-impossible-7-trailer-tom-cruise-train-stunt/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Should Beginners Trade Binary Options?</title>
		<link>http://us.yorba.org/how-to-trade-binary-options/</link>
					<comments>http://us.yorba.org/how-to-trade-binary-options/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[usyorba]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:51:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Beginners]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[options]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trade]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://us.yorba.org/?p=85</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Trading in financial markets can be a daunting prospect for beginners, especially on how to trade binary options. Binary trading, in particular, requires a certain level of knowledge and skill to be...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/how-to-trade-binary-options/">How Should Beginners Trade Binary Options?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p></p>
<p><a href="https://kiiky.com/wealth/?s=Trading">Trading</a> in financial markets can be a daunting prospect for beginners, especially on how to trade binary options. Binary trading, in particular, requires a certain level of knowledge and skill to be successful. </p>
<p>In this article, we will explore some tips and strategies that beginners can use to trade binary options effectively.</p>
<p>See: <a href="https://kiiky.com/wealth/how-to-make-money-with-binary-options/">How to Make Money with Binary Options in 2023: Full Hacks</a></p>
<p>Understanding Binary Trading Options</p>
<p>Before diving into the world of binary trading, it is essential to understand what it entails. Binary trading involves predicting whether the price of a given asset will rise or fall within a specified time frame. </p>
<p>Traders must choose a binary options broker and then select an asset to trade. They will then need to determine the direction of the asset’s price movement and the time frame for the trade.</p>
<p>1. Choosing a Broker</p>
<p>The first step for beginners looking to trade binary options is to choose a reputable binary options broker. If you are completely new to it, we recommend testing <a href="https://www.binaryoptions.com/broker/olymp-trade/">test of the Olymp Trade Broker</a>, which is a reliable and proven platform. The broker should be licensed and regulated by the relevant authorities to ensure the safety of funds and fair trading practices. Beginners should also consider the broker’s platform and the range of tools and resources offered.</p>
<p>Regulation and License: A regulated broker will offer greater protection to your investments and ensure that your funds are secure. It is important to ensure that the broker you choose is licensed and regulated by a reputable authority such as the Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) in the UK or the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) in the US.</p>
<p>Trading Platform: The platform should be user-friendly and easy to navigate, even for beginners. It should also offer a range of tools and resources that can help you make informed trading decisions. </p>
<p>Asset Selection: Beginners should choose a broker that offers a wide range of assets such as stocks, commodities, and currencies. This will allow you to diversify your portfolio and reduce your risk.</p>
<p>Customer Support: Look for brokers that offer 24/7 customer support through multiple channels such as phone, email, and live chat. </p>
<p>Demo Accounts: This is a great way for beginners to get a feel for trading and to test out different strategies. </p>
<p>Fees and Commissions: Look for brokers that offer competitive fees and commissions, as this can have a significant impact on your overall profitability. </p>
<p>See also: <a href="https://kiiky.com/wealth/world-series-of-poker/">Rolling in Dough: Tips for Winning Big at the World Series of Poker</a></p>
<p>2. Developing a Trading Strategy</p>
<p>A solid strategy is essential for success in binary. Beginners should spend time developing a strategy that aligns with their goals and risk tolerance. This involves conducting market analysis and identifying potential opportunities. </p>
<p>Traders should also establish entry and exit points and set stop-loss orders to manage risk.</p>
<p>Here are some popular strategies that beginners can consider when developing their binary strategy:</p>
<p>Trend: This strategy involves analyzing the market trends and trading in the direction of the trend. </p>
<p>Breakout: This strategy involves identifying key levels of support and resistance and trading the breakouts. </p>
<p>Price Action: This strategy assumes analyzing the price movements of the asset and making trading decisions based on price patterns and candlestick formations. </p>
<p>News: This strategy involves trading based on news events and economic data releases. </p>
<p>Risk: This strategy involves simultaneously buying a call option and selling a put option or vice versa. </p>
<p>3. Managing Risk when Trading Binary Options</p>
<p>Effective risk management is crucial for success in binary. Beginners should only risk a small percentage of their capital on each trade to minimize potential losses. They should also set stop-loss orders to limit their losses if the trade does not go as planned.</p>
<p>Read also: <a href="https://kiiky.com/wealth/how-to-make-money-from-option-trading/">How to Make Money from Option Trading in 2023</a></p>
<p>4. Using Trading Tools</p>
<p>Binary platforms offer a range of trading tools and resources that beginners can use to make informed trading decisions. These include charts, technical analysis indicators, and economic calendars. Beginners should take advantage of these tools to conduct market analysis and identify potential opportunities.</p>
<p>5. Starting Small</p>
<p>For beginners, it is advisable to start with small trades and gradually increase the trade size as they become more experienced and confident in their trading strategy. This approach allows traders to learn from their mistakes without risking a significant amount of capital.</p>
<p>6. Staying Disciplined</p>
<p>Trading binary requires discipline and patience. Beginners should stick to their strategy and avoid making impulsive decisions based on emotions. It is also essential to maintain a trading journal to track progress and identify areas for improvement.</p>
<p>7. Continuing Education</p>
<p>Learning should be a continuous process for traders. Beginners should invest time in learning about trading strategies, market analysis, and risk management. </p>
<p>They should also keep up with the latest news and trends in the financial markets to identify potential trading opportunities.</p>
<p>See also: <a href="https://kiiky.com/wealth/sell-put-options/">How To Sell Put Options To Get Profit In Any Market</a></p>
<p>Final Thoughts</p>
<p>Binary trading can be a lucrative form of <a href="https://kiiky.com/wealth/forex-trading-in-nigeria/">trading for beginners</a> with the right knowledge, skills, and discipline. </p>
<p>By following the tips and strategies on how to trade binary outlined in this article, beginners can increase their chances of success in the binary market. With practice and patience, beginners can become successful binary traders.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/how-to-trade-binary-options/">How Should Beginners Trade Binary Options?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://us.yorba.org/how-to-trade-binary-options/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Latest Jacob deGrom injury update is worst-case scenario for Rangers</title>
		<link>http://us.yorba.org/rangers-jacob-degrom-tommy-john-worst-case/</link>
					<comments>http://us.yorba.org/rangers-jacob-degrom-tommy-john-worst-case/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[usyorba]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:50:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[deGrom]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[injury]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jacob]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Latest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rangers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[scenario]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[update]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[worstcase]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://us.yorba.org/?p=81</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Texas Rangers were hoping that ace Jacob deGrom would progress while rehabbing from his elbow injury. Now, his season is over.The Texas Rangers, in need of starting pitching help, made a...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/rangers-jacob-degrom-tommy-john-worst-case/">Latest Jacob deGrom injury update is worst-case scenario for Rangers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p> The Texas Rangers were hoping that ace Jacob deGrom would progress while rehabbing from his elbow injury. Now, his season is over.The <a href="https://fansided.com/mlb/mlb-teams/texas-rangers/">Texas Rangers</a>, in need of starting pitching help, made a huge gamble this past winter. That being, they signed former New York Mets ace Jacob deGrom to a five-year, $185 million contract. While he is one of the best pitchers in the game, he had been unbelievably injury prone the previous two years. But, the Rangers hoped that they could have him at full health.On Monday, <a href="https://fansided.com/2023/06/05/rangers-concede-defeat-jacob-degrom-injury-status/">the Rangers placed deGrom on the 60-day injured list</a> with right elbow inflammation that forced him from his Apr. 28 start against the New York Yankees. The team would send him to undergo another MRI on Tuesday to see how he was progressing.Unfortunately for deGrom, his debut season with the Rangers is officially over. As first reported by Evan Grant of the Dallas Morning News, deGrom is set to undergo Tommy John surgery to repair a tear in his UCL. The full extent of the tear won’t be known until he undergoes surgery, which is scheduled for next week.To clarify: Full extent of surgery will be determined once Dr Keith Meister gets inside of elbow. For now: Ligament repair. That doesn’t rule out something like an internal brace. Either way: Out at least 12 months <a href="https://t.co/Or6mRXmbOZ">https://t.co/Or6mRXmbOZ</a>— Evan Grant (@Evan_P_Grant) <a href="https://twitter.com/Evan_P_Grant/status/1666185627019116544?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 6, 2023</a>Jacob deGrom’s debut season with Rangers is over, as he’s set to undergo Tommy John surgeryIt has been a rough couple of years for deGrom. He missed the second half of the 2021 season with the Mets due to right elbow inflammation. Then in 2022, deGrom missed the start of the campaign due to a stress reaction of his right scapula.Unfortunately, the injuries carried over into his first year with Texas. At the start of spring training, deGrom was limited with left-side tightness. Then, in mid-April, he left a start against the Kansas City Royals due to right wrist soreness. His latest injury scare turned out to be one that would end his season after just six starts.deGrom has recorded a 2.67 ERA, a 0.758 WHIP, 45 strikeouts, and four walks in 30.1 innings.The Rangers have been performing well without deGrom, but this is the worst news they could have gotten. deGrom was supposed to play a pivotal role in the team making it back to the postseason for the first time since 2016. Now, he will be out until midway through the 2024 season. <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/rangers-jacob-degrom-tommy-john-worst-case/">Latest Jacob deGrom injury update is worst-case scenario for Rangers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://us.yorba.org/rangers-jacob-degrom-tommy-john-worst-case/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>&#039;Stamped From The Beginning&#039;: History of Racism in America Gets Graphic Novel Adaptation</title>
		<link>http://us.yorba.org/stamped-from-beginning-graphic-novel-racism-american-history/</link>
					<comments>http://us.yorba.org/stamped-from-beginning-graphic-novel-racism-american-history/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[usyorba]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:48:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Movie]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[039Stamped]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adaptation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[America]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Beginning039]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Graphic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Racism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://us.yorba.org/?p=74</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A vitally important and visually stunning new graphic novel, Stamped from the Beginning: The Definitive History of Racist Ideas in America, adapts MacArthur Genius Grant winner Dr. Ibram X. Kendi&#8217;s 2016 book...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/stamped-from-beginning-graphic-novel-racism-american-history/">&#039;Stamped From The Beginning&#039;: History of Racism in America Gets Graphic Novel Adaptation</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img decoding="async" src="https://static1.srcdn.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/stamped-from-the-beginning.jpg" /><br />
A vitally important and visually stunning new graphic novel, Stamped from the Beginning: The Definitive History of Racist Ideas in America, adapts MacArthur Genius Grant winner Dr. Ibram X. Kendi&#8217;s 2016 book of the same name. This new medium makes Kendi&#8217;s acclaimed history book more accessible and digestible to a variety of readers.</p>
<p>Kendi is a National Book Award-winning historian and the founder and director of Boston University&#8217;s Center for Antiracist Research. He worked closely with award-winning cartoonist and historian Joel Christian Gill to adapt Stamped from the Beginning into the graphic novel format. Their collaboration gives the critically necessary text new life in 2023 amidst continued violence against Black and Brown bodies across the United States.<br />
SCREENRANT VIDEO OF THE DAYSCROLL TO CONTINUE WITH CONTENT</p>
<p>Stamped from the Beginning: The Definitive History of Racist Ideas in America is an impressive and disturbing weaving of the United States&#8217; horrifically racist roots, the institutional and interpersonal racism still pervasive in American society today, and the ways in which antiracist movements can inspire hope and change. These important lessons are all wrapped up in truly gorgeous and evocative art by Joel Christian Gill for the new graphic novel format.</p>
<p>Racism has persisted throughout history—but so have antiracist efforts to dismantle it. Through deep research and a gripping narrative that illuminates the lives of five key American figures, preeminent historian Ibram X. Kendi reveals how understanding and improving the world cannot happen without identifying and facing the racist forces that shape it.</p>
<p>Related: <a href="https://screenrant.com/run-john-lewis-march-graphic-novel-civil-rights/">Rep. John Lewis&#8217; RUN Tells the Untold Story of the Civil Rights Movement</a></p>
<p> Confronting America&#8217;s Racist Past, Present, and Potential Future </p>
<p>Kendi argues that &#8220;&#8230;the root of these tragedies&#8230; is a lineage of racist ideas that have endured and continue to be reproduced throughout the history and present of the United States, ideas that continually justify racist policies.&#8221; This new graphic novel was adapted beginning in 2020 amidst protests caused by the murders of Breonna Taylor, Ahmaud Arbery, Jacob Blake <a href="https://screenrant.com/do-right-thing-george-floyd-protest-video-spike-lee/">and George Floyd</a>. It aims to make complex ideas about race and racism, and the history of how racism has shaped and continues to guide the United States, very digestible to a variety of readers who may have little exposure to this topic. This adaptation is incredibly important because the more people who gain access to the critically important writings of Kendi, the more the public can understand the impact of conservative politicians&#8217; battles against things like <a href="https://screenrant.com/keeping-up-kardashians-caitlyn-jenner-race-schools-politics/">Critical Race Theory being taught in schools</a>.</p>
<p>Stamped from the Beginning shows that unfiltered history, truth, accountability, and pursuit of justice are the critical components of building an antiracist culture and future, ideals that are being destroyed by recent movements towards book banning and resegregation. The new graphic novel adaptation is a vast and decades spanning history of how racist ideas first rooted in America. It is grounded in the exploration of five key American figures who have impacted the development and change of the United States since its founding: Cotton Mather, Thomas Jefferson, William Lloyd Garrison, W.E.B. Du Bois, and Angela Davis. Stamped from the Beginning made a major splash in the world of politics, education, and antiracist activism when it first debuted in 2016. Now the &#8220;culture defining&#8221; text is even more necessary than ever, making the graphic novel adaptation&#8217;s accessibility to younger readers and those unfamiliar with its concepts and histories even more critical.</p>
<p>Kendi&#8217;s book was a critical and imperative text when it first debuted in 2016. This stunning new graphic novel adaptation of Stamped from the Beginning: The Definitive History of Racist Ideas in America comes at a time when racial justice and antiracist activism is facing more pushback than has been seen in years, making its approachability and illustrated breakdowns of racist ideas and their impact more important than ever.</p>
<p>Stamped from the Beginning: The Definitive History of Racist Ideas in America is available now.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/stamped-from-beginning-graphic-novel-racism-american-history/">&#039;Stamped From The Beginning&#039;: History of Racism in America Gets Graphic Novel Adaptation</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://us.yorba.org/stamped-from-beginning-graphic-novel-racism-american-history/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
