<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>rumors Archives - Yorba Foundation</title>
	<atom:link href="http://us.yorba.org/tag/rumors/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://us.yorba.org/tag/rumors/</link>
	<description>USA</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:46:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Braves rumors: 3 superstar pitcher trades to fix the issue, 2 budget options to help</title>
		<link>http://us.yorba.org/braves-trade-rumors-superstars-budget/</link>
					<comments>http://us.yorba.org/braves-trade-rumors-superstars-budget/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[usyorba]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:46:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Braves]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[budget]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fix]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[issue]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[options]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pitcher]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[rumors]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[superstar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[trades]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://us.yorba.org/?p=65</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shane Bieber, Cleveland Guardians. (Photo by Ron Schwane/Getty Images)The Atlanta Braves are still trying to find answers for the rotation and the trade market could heat up with superstars and budget options...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/braves-trade-rumors-superstars-budget/">Braves rumors: 3 superstar pitcher trades to fix the issue, 2 budget options to help</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shane Bieber, Cleveland Guardians. (Photo by Ron Schwane/Getty Images)The Atlanta Braves are still trying to find answers for the rotation and the trade market could heat up with superstars and budget options both available.It’s frankly somewhat remarkable that the <a href="https://fansided.com/2023/06/06/braves-rumors-soroka-mets-contract/">Atlanta Braves</a> have been as dominant in the 2023 season given the issues they’ve had with pitching, specifically the rotation as the bullpen has started to round into form.Injuries to Max Fried, Kyle Wright and Ian Anderson have put them behind the 8-ball and manager Brian Snitker has left no stone unturned trying to find replacements to help them through this time. But Michael Soroka was optioned back to Triple-A after two up-and-down starts, Dylan Dodd has been inconsistent as well, and the bullpen games yielded unkind results.With Fried being moved to the 60-day IL, a lack of faith in Soroka after his first two starts, and a potential reluctance to elevate 20-year-old AJ Smith-Shawver into a starting role so soon after he started the season in Single-A, it might be time for Alex Anthopoulos and the Braves to finally get active on the trade market.But in that light, do the <a href="https://fansided.com/2023/06/04/braves-rumors-brewers-trade-targets/">Atlanta Braves</a> target superstars in a trade to possibly fix the issue long term, or rather look to more budget-friendly options that can be helpful to get through this season? Let’s take a look at both with three stars and two budget options the Braves could trade for.Braves trade rumors: 3 superstars to fix pitching issues, 2 budget options5. Shane Bieber would be a Cy Young-caliber fix for the Braves long termBubbling under the surface in Cleveland has been the possibility that the Guardians would move former Cy Young winner Shane Bieber at the MLB Trade Deadline. He’s in the next to last year of club control before he’ll be a free agent and extension talks have not been particularly fruitful.If the Guardians are going to trade Bieber, though, that’s a market that the <a href="https://fansided.com/2023/06/03/braves-rumors-3-trades-2-avoid/">Atlanta Braves</a> would be completely foolish to not sniff around in.Bieber hasn’t been as dominant this season as in some year’s past, but he’s still been a high-end starting pitcher. Through 12 starts, the 28-year-old has posted a 3.72 ERA with a 1.29 WHIP. A minor issue early on has been a decline in his K/BB ration to 2.5, well below his career-worst of 4.1 for a season. But that has started to rebound.You also simply can’t forget how unhittable he’s been at times, most notably in the shortened 2020 season when he won the AL Cy Young in which he posted an absurd 1.63 ERA and 0.87 WHIP over 12 starts with Cleveland.Anthopoulous and the Braves have made their bones about trading for guys at the end of club control and then locking them up on extensions. If that’s the route that they choose to go to address the issues with the rotation, Bieber is about as good of an option as you could imagine.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/braves-trade-rumors-superstars-budget/">Braves rumors: 3 superstar pitcher trades to fix the issue, 2 budget options to help</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://us.yorba.org/braves-trade-rumors-superstars-budget/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>NBA rumors: Kyrie Irving claims LeBron reports weren’t a ploy to get to LA</title>
		<link>http://us.yorba.org/nba-rumors-kyrie-irving-lebron-trade-lakers/</link>
					<comments>http://us.yorba.org/nba-rumors-kyrie-irving-lebron-trade-lakers/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[usyorba]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:18:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[claims]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Irving]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kyrie]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LeBron]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NBA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ploy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[reports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[rumors]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[werent]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://us.yorba.org/?p=41</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Despite rampant speculation suggesting otherwise, Kyrie Irving is apparently content to re-sign with the Dallas Mavericks. Kyrie Irving has been tied to LeBron James and the Los Angeles Lakers since before the trade...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/nba-rumors-kyrie-irving-lebron-trade-lakers/">NBA rumors: Kyrie Irving claims LeBron reports weren’t a ploy to get to LA</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p> Despite rampant speculation suggesting otherwise, Kyrie Irving is apparently content to re-sign with the Dallas Mavericks. Kyrie Irving has been tied to LeBron James and the <a href="https://fansided.com/nba/nba-teams/los-angeles-lakers/">Los Angeles Lakers</a> since before the trade deadline last season. The disgruntled star was traded from Brooklyn to Dallas in the final year of an expiring contract and, to add fuel to the fire of speculation, the <a href="https://fansided.com/nba/nba-teams/dallas-mavericks/">Mavs</a> missed the playoffs despite a statistically fruitful partnership between Kyrie and Luka Doncic.Irving then went on to attend multiple Lakers playoff games, leading some to believe he was angling to get in the good graces of LeBron and the Lakers’ front office. Irving famously demanded a trade away from LeBron in Cleveland but has since seen the error in his ways.<a href="https://marcstein.substack.com/p/lebron-and-the-mavericks?r=o66it&amp;utm_campaign=post&amp;utm_medium=email" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">New reporting from NBA insider Marc Stein</a>, however, paints a different picture of Irving’s upcoming free agency.Kyrie Irving wants to re-sign with the Dallas Mavericks“Two sources close to the process insisted Monday that Irving has consistently expressed a desire to remain a Maverick and actually wants to shut down the notion that he’s angling to get to L.A.”That kind of sentiment will come as a surprise to many, especially those among the LA faithful who were hoping for Kyrie to push the Lakers over the finish line. That said, the Mavs have every financial advantage to keep Irving. Meanwhile, the Lakers are not interested in the idea of reuniting LeBron with his former co-champion, <a href="https://theathletic.com/4582508/2023/06/05/kyrie-lebron-mavericks-lakers/?source=emp_shared_article" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">according to Jovan Buha of The Athletic</a>.This feels like a perfect storm of those two facts: Irving can get the most money from Dallas and the Lakers don’t want him or the headache he traditionally brings with him. Irving probably enjoys playing with Luka Doncic too. Just because last season ended poorly doesn’t mean 2023-24 will end the same way.Irving and Doncic form arguably the most skilled, potent guard duo in the NBA. Irving is <a href="https://fansided.com/2023/06/05/kyrie-irving-lebron-trade-twitter/">openly recruiting LeBron to Dallas</a>, to really drive home his desire to stick around. The logistics of that hypothetical transaction are <a href="https://fansided.com/2023/06/06/5-assets-mavericks-acquire-lebron-james/">borderline unfathomable</a>, but hey — it’s a nice thought.Irving and LeBron have progressed past the conflict that once mired their relationship and Irving evidently has a place where he’s happy playing basketball. This feels like a win all around. Don’t expect Irving and James to team up any time soon, but get excited for the next year-plus of Irving and Luka dancing on hapless defenders. </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org/nba-rumors-kyrie-irving-lebron-trade-lakers/">NBA rumors: Kyrie Irving claims LeBron reports weren’t a ploy to get to LA</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://us.yorba.org">Yorba Foundation</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://us.yorba.org/nba-rumors-kyrie-irving-lebron-trade-lakers/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
